al
al
[Music]
[Música]
ah
ah
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
[Music]
[Música]
Oh Oh
Oh Oh
ha
ha
[Music]
[Música]
ah ah
ah ah
P
P
[Music]
[Música]
titito
titito
Hello grandpa cacao 4 Love cacao 4 Love I
Hola abuelo cacao 4 Love cacao 4 Love
just saw pixi donating on the Canal
Acabo de ver a pixi donando en el Canal
de Roma and I thought of you pix doesn't come around
de Roma y he pensado en ti ya no se pasa
here anymore two points
pix por aquí dos puntos
a hug from the pregnant woman from
un abrazo de la mujer embarazada de
biena smiling face a hug
biena cara sonriente un abrazo mujer
pregnant woman from colala lumpur Pixi
embarazada de colala lumpur El pixi
was here donating one of these last
estuvo aquí donando uno de estos últimos
days Tito taí Tito Tito Tito
días Tito taí
tatito Tito Tito
tatito Tito Tito
[Music]
[Música]
ti
ti
tatio
tatio
[Music]
[Música]
ti the last one and we're leaving okay
ti la última y nos vamos vale
Marciano took  300,000 told me
Marciano se llevó 300.000 me lo han
today
dicho hoy
[Music]
[Música]
man And where can I see the Martian thing
tío Y dónde se ve lo de marciano
stomach hurts when I breathe
me duele el abdomen cuando respiro
hard
fuerte
[Music]
[Música]
T
T
P
P
[Music]
[Música]
Oh what a [ __ ] hour
Ay qué hora tan golfa
ah
ah
[Music]
[Música]
Hey well my goodness my goodness today we have some
Eh bueno madre mía madre mía hoy tenemos
gossip here let's see eh Piece by
aquí chisme a ver eh Por partes por
piece I'm going to move the camera away a
partes voy a alejar la cámara un
little Oh how chill But what what
poco Ay qué chill Pero qué qué horitas
[ __ ] hours always here with the kids
más golfa siempre aquí en la chavalería
eh what a [ __ ] hour always here with
eh qué horita es más golfas siempre aquí
the kids I don't know where to start
en la chavalería no sé por dónde empezar
man I don't know if I should start with Win michu
tío No sé si empezar por lo de Win michu
or with anug or with well
o por lo de anug o por lo de bueno lo
we'll see everything in the
vamos a ver todo al
end let's see about Win michu Win
final a ver lo de Win michu lo de Win
michu shorter Win michu
michu más corto lo de Win michu más
shorter what are you talking about what are you talking about
corto de qué habláis de qué habláis por
there and delox well delox let's see about it I
ahí y delox bueno delox a ver delo
wanted to come tomorrow but tomorrow the other one
quería venir mañana pero mañana el otro
and I think I think that  They're going to say they're
y creo que creo que me van a decir de
coming next week, but oh well, it's
venir la semana que viene pero bueno o
trite, imo, the topic is already trite,
sea trills imo el tema Ya eh trillados
the topic of cryptocurrencies and what
el tema Ya de las criptomonedas y y lo
is that you are still a rascal, grandpa,
es que tú eres aún un golfillo abuelo
but yes, cacao 4 Love, cacao 4 Love, cacao 4
pero s cacao 4 Love cacao 4 Love cacao 4
Love, it's also true, it's also true.
Love también es verdad también es verdad
A little bit of a rascal, yes, that we are that this
Un poquillo golfillo s que somos
topic is trite, the topic of
que que est trilla es el tema Ya de las
cryptocurrencies, eh, but it's still causing a
criptomonedas eh pero está dando todavía
stir because they just told me
que hablar porque me acaban de avisar
right now I'm seeing it here that
ahora mismo lo estoy viendo aquí que
Ricky Ed has taken a dig at
Ricky Ed le ha pegado una pulla al
Dallas and
Dallas y
that he has arrived, a dig at Dallas and
que que el llegado una pua al Dallas y
that Dallas has made a video
que el el Dallas le ha hecho un vídeo
answering utbh or flameo So
contestando a utbh o flameo Entonces lo
we're going to see it now, for sure, let's get
vamos a ver ahora segurísimo vamos a
rid of the wismichu thing. The wismichu thing
quitarnos lo de wismichu lo de wismichu
is quick. Well, let's get rid of the
es rapidito Bueno vamos a quitarnos lo
wismichu thing, but if it's that all the
de wismichu pero si es que son todos los
topics are, all the powerful topics,
temas son todos los temas potentes en
really today, eh, I think, eh, I think all
verdad hoy eh creo yo eh creo que todos
the topics are powerful, let's see Win michu
los temas están potentes a ver Win michu
has spoken about Dallas again, even if he does
ha vuelto a hablar de Dallas que aunque
n't mention it. Well, I think that well  It's
no lo mencione Pues yo creo que bueno es
pretty obvious that he's talking
bastante evidente no que está hablando
about Dallas for several reasons, first
de Dallas por varios motivo en primer
of all, not only because he knows it,
lugar bueno no solamente porque lo sepa
but because, well, let's see, now when you
sino porque bueno a ver ahora cuando
read the text you're going to understand me,
leáis el texto me vais a entender yo
personally, okay. And I say this, I
personalmente vale Y esto lo digo te lo
promise you without prejudice or anything like
prometo sin prejuicios ni nada por el
that. But if I've been listening to this man, I do
estilo Pero si yo llevo a este hombre
n't know how long or
escuchándolo no sé cuánto el tiempo y
how many times. I don't think the last
cuántas ocasiones No creo que la última
time we talked about Win
vez que hablamos de Win
Michu was about Club 13 and
michu fue lo de fue lo del Club 13 y
that's precisely when I said it again. No, no, I'm not
precisamente ahí lo volví a decir no no
going to mention Dallas, I'm not going to
no voy a mencionar a Dallas no voy a
talk about Dallas because if not, it's going to
hablar de Dallas porque si no me va a
be 70 videos. I personally believe
ser 70 vídeos yo personalmente creo
that you don't want to close that page of your
que no quieres cerrar esa página de tu
life and you don't want each one of you to be going about
vida y no quieres que cada uno estéis
your lives without mentioning, okay, I
haciendo vuestra vida sin mencionar vale
mean, if not, don't look for it.
o sea si no no lo busca yo de este
What I get from this message is that, uh, you don't want
mensaje lo que saco es que eh No quieres
Dallas to mention you when Dasas is
que Dallas te mencione cuando dasas está
strong, but when Dasas is at a
potente pero cuando dasas está en un
low point, like it is now, uh, there are a
momento Bajo como es ahora no que eh Hay
lot of people,
mucha gente que la mayoría de la gente
I think most people are not supporting it
yo creo que no lo está apoyando
in the media, that's what's happening
mediáticamente es lo que está pasando
with the cryptocurrency, so they take advantage of it
con la criptomoneda pues ahí aprovecha
to actually mention it.
para de hecho mencionar el tema de la
cryptocurrency issue to see if by hitting it
criptomoneda para ver si pegándole un
off eh in the media war that you
palito eh en la guerra mediática que
two have, since Dallas
tenéis los dos pues como el Dallas ahora
is going through a bad moment now, they'll take
está en un mal momento pues se ponen de
your side because it has nothing to do with
tu lado con es que no tiene nada que ver
yours, I mean, Dallas could fall. But
lo tuyo con o sea Dallas puede caer Pero
that's not going to take away from the fact that what has been
eso no va a quitar que lo que se te haya
criticized about you or what or the war that
criticado a ti o lo que o la guerra que
you've had with him, they're going to prove you
tú hayas tenido con él te vayan a dar la
right. I'm seeing this a lot, eh. And I don't
razón esto lo estoy viendo mucho eh Y no
understand why, from here, I'm
entiendo el por qué ya desde aquí yo me
Costa. I
Costa yé
see that, well, there's not going to be much attention paid to
que a ver no se le va a dar mucha bola a
this in the media for the moment, okay, but I have
esto mediáticamente de momento vale pero
seen how,
sí que he visto como que
mm, both he and those around him on several
mm tanto él como en su entorno en varias
occasions, like they're once again
ocasiones como que están otra vez
looking, uh, for the answer to their mouths, I don't
buscando no eh la respuesta a la boca no
know. Why, I don't know if it's because they want to
sé el Por qué no sé si es que quieren
have another chance to see if they're
volver a tener una oportunidad a ver si
right this time,
en esta ocasión tienen la razón
but it doesn't make sense. I mean, if you, if
pero que no tiene sentido O sea si tú si
you want a person to leave you
tú quieres que una persona te deje en
alone and not come out tomorrow and you because
paz y no te salga mañana y te porque
this is so that they hit you with a sasc,
esto es para que te pegue un sasc caso
the Dallas case because this. Now I. This
el Dallas porque esto Ahora yo Esto no
is not al  100% just as it is being told
es al 100% tal y como lo está contando
Here and Now tomorrow Dallas comes out, they will
Aquí y ahora mañana sale el Dallas te
file a SASC case against you and how bad
mete un sasc caso y hay qu malo es el
Dallas is and they are obsessed with Win michu
Dallas y está obsesionado con Win michu
okay today I had a trial for
vale hoy tenía un juicio por una
alleged unfair competition that I have been
supuesta competencia desleal que llevo
wanting to be held for years to
años queriendo que se celebre para
finally close a stage of my life okay you
cerrar al fin una etapa de mi vida vale
want to close this stage of your life
quieres cerrar esta etapa de tu vida
then the best idea is to put a tweet
entonces la mejor idea es poner un tweet
that moves the hornets' nest you don't want to close
que mueva la avispero no quieres cerrar
a stage of your life
una etapa de tu vida le quieres pegar
you want to hit dala for the cryptocurrency okay And on top of that you want to how uh distort or or imply how well maybe Dallas doesn't want to do that trial because they are afraid of doing that trial okay everyone knows that their lawyer said in a
mundo sabe lo dijo su abogado en un
video that Dallas filed a
vídeo que Dallas le puso una demanda
civil suit against wismichu apart from the criminal one not that
civil a wismichu aparte de la penal no
wismichu was acquitted eh in that
que absolvieron a wismichu eh en ese
trial
juicio
no jetzer a kiss the opposing party and
no jetzer un beso la parte contraria y
plaintiff has already delayed it about three
demandante ya lo ha [__] unas tres
times always with arguments that are not very
veces siempre con argumentos poco
understandable let's see the opposing party
comprensibles a ver la parte contraria
has not delayed it  the judge suspends the
no lo ha [__] lo suspende el juez
court the sec I don't know who's
el juzgado el sec no sé quién es el
in charge if it's the secretary if it's the one that's
encargado si es el secretario si es el
worth it But Dallas doesn't decide
que vale Pero el Dallas no decide tú
imagine a trial in which they
imagínate un juicio en el que a mí me
sue me and I say [ __ ] it I'm going to do it I'm
demanden que yo diga [__] [__] lo voy
not interested in this trial I'm putting it
a no me interesa este juicio lo voy
off forever I'm putting it
retrasando toda la vida lo voy
off I'm never going to go for decades no no let's
retrasando no voy nunca décadas no no a
see yes yes if they
ver si si si lo
suspend it if they suspend it it's because the
suspenden si lo suspenden es porque el
reason is valid if they suspend it it's
motivo es válido si lo suspenden es
because the reason is valid I don't know
porque el motivo es válido yo no sé
what the other reasons are eh on this
cuáles son los otros motivos eh en esta
occasion today I did find out why it was
ocasión el de hoy si supe porque se ha
clear I'm not going to find out of course I did find out
claro no lo voy a saber claro que supe
why it was suspended I'm not I
porque se ha suspendido yo no estoy yo
'm completely in disagreement and it
estoy completamente en desacuerdo y me
seems to me that on the part of the court it's a
parece por parte del juzgado una
joke that they suspended it okay
payasada que lo hayan suspendido vale
but the thing is that he has too I
pero es que él también yo tengo
understand that he has suspended it on
entendido que lo ha suspendido en
some occasions or that he has asked for it to be
algunas ocasiones o que ha pedido que se
suspended because a document was missing I don't know what I mean
suspenda porque faltaba un oficio no sé
Here he is not telling
qué O sea Es que aquí no está diciendo
the truth if you're going to say it I have
la verdad si lo vas a decilo yo lo he
suspended it a few times and other times he
suspendido algunas veces y otras veces
has suspended it the other one okay it's that they
la ha suspendido el otro vale es que son
want Dallas to come wismi but they
ganas de que venga el Dallas wismi pero
are consequences  of your actions are
son consecuencias de tus actos más
rather not consequences, let's see, they are Of
bien no son consecuencias a ver son
course it's normal with the video he
Claro que es normal con el vídeo que
made It's normal for the other person to
hizo Es normal que el otro le ponga una
sue him but I don't know if he would have shot
demanda pero yo no sé si hubiera tirado
That's why I'm looking forward to knowing how
Por esto estoy deseando saber cómo va
this trial goes because I think it's the
este juicio porque creo que es la
first time that we're going to see a trial for
primera vez que vamos a ver un juicio de
unfair competition for two
competencia desleal por dos canales de
YouTube channels because in part it makes sense
YouTube porque en parte tiene su sentido
no because They would be like two companies no eh of
no porque Serían como dos empresas no eh
course and if there are lies and there are things
claro y si hay mentiras y hay cosas
no but of course I would have seen more
no pero claro yo lo hubiera visto más
sense in a lawsuit for honor I would have
sentido a una demanda por honor yo lo
seen eh a sense a
hubiera visto eh una sentido una demanda
civil lawsuit for honor I mean no No Not
civil por honor O sea no No Haber puesto
even having put the penalty and having gone with him eh
la pena siquiera y haber ido con él eh
for him with the honor okay But well the
por él con el honor vale Pero bueno las
strategies that the lawyer has eh from
estrategias que tenga el abogado eh de
Dallas okay no he's not a lawyer who
Dallas vale que no no es un abogado que
handles anything of mine by the way and no I don't know He will
lleve nada mío por cierto e no no sé Él
know I in part it makes sense no But
sabrá yo en parte tiene sentido no Pero
well we'll see we'll see we can't
bueno ya lo veremos ya lo veremos no
jump to conclusions before we've already hit our
podemos sacar conclusiones antes que ya
mouths many times for
nos hemos dado muchas veces la boca por
jumping to conclusions before time but
sacar conclusiones antes de tiempo pero
[ __ ] [ __ ] it's no no the truth is that you
[__] [__] es no no la verdad es que lo
're selling it here as if the other one
estás vendiendo aquí como que el otro lo
is suspending it because he's afraid of
está suspendiendo porque tiene miedo a
your trial let's see if  the other is the one
tu juicio vamos a ver si el otro es el
who sues you know but apart from that the
que demanda sabes pero que aparte la
suspension is not decided by
suspensión no la decide el
Dallas and on this occasion not even
Dallas y en esta ocasión ni siquiera el
Dallas has requested that it be suspended
Dallas ha solicitado que lo suspendan
okay I think that with today's there is four
vale creo que con la de hoy van cuatro
the excuse on this occasion was that since it is a
la excusa en esta ocasión era que al ser
holiday in Seville one of the Witnesses
festivo en Sevilla uno de los Testigos
could not
no podía
testify coincidentally I am also in
declarar casualmente Yo también estoy en
Seville until Sunday and despite it
Sevilla hasta el domingo y pese a ser
being a holiday there are still flights to travel to Barcelona like every day in fact I had bought mine to go up and down after having slept less than 4 hours because of the great ACDC concert that I was able to enjoy last night you can't imagine how I was in the streets with the
cómo estaba en las calles con el tema
concert By the way
del concierto Por cierto
eem the trial has not been
eem el juicio no es que se haya
suspended because the witness from Seville
suspendido porque el testigo de Sevilla
cannot
no pueda
testify the witness from Seville and this
declarar el testigo de Sevilla y esto
[ __ ] It's that this is that this is
[__] Es que esto es que esto está
entered It's that this is not true the
entado Es que esto no es verdad el
witness from Seville when there are so many
testigo de Sevilla cuando hay tantos
kilometers of distance okay I
kilómetros de distancia vale Yo
normally on some occasions I go if it's
normalmente en algunas ocasiones voy si
not convenient for me then I don't go but we are
no me pilla bien pues no voy pero
talking I think it's 100 km
estamos hablando creo que son de 100 km
so let's see if you are talking to me that this
entonces a ver si me estás hablando que
is a judgment of mine Maybe life or
es un juicio mío A lo mejor de vida o
death I who know something more maybe then I come
muerte yo que sé algo más tal pues me
closer  I take the car like I've done on
acerco cojo el coche como he hecho en
other occasions, I get closer, I take a plane
otras ocasiones me acerco Cojo un avión
and I get closer and then I come back whatever
y me acerco y luego vuelvo lo que sea
okay on this occasion Well, it didn't suit me
vale en esta ocasión Pues no me venía
Why Well, because it's a long weekend here
bien Por qué Pues porque aquí es puente
because the children are on break
porque los niños están de descanso
because I have a lot of
porque tengo teng un montón de movidas
family issues because I have to help my
familiares porque tengo que ayudar a mis
parents with many things, go to Barcelona
padres por muchas cosas irme a Barcelona
to get in for what 20 minutes, half an hour
para entrar el qué 20 minutos media hora
to testify about something that I don't know if what
a testificar una cosa que no sé si
I'm going to contribute is going to
tampoco lo que yo vaya a aportar que va
be my opinion and my perspective No, what can I
a ser mi opinión y mi perspectiva No qué
tell you? No, then the witness from
te digo no entonces el testigo de
Seville requested uh to
Sevilla lo que solicitó fue eh
testify by
testificar por
video call, it's a super common thing, it
videollamada es una cosa super común no
's not an excuse or anything crazy
es ninguna excusa ni nada descabellado
okay, I've done it in almost all the
vale lo he hecho en casi y todos los
trials that I've been to as a witness, I think
juicios a los que he ido de testigo creo
in all of them, in fact in almost all of them okay,
que en todos de hecho en casi todos vale
the court this court
el el juzgado este juzgado pues se
insisted that I had to give them my
empeñó en que yo tenía que darle Mi
address and that I had to go and that I don't know
dirección y que tenía que ir y que no sé
what and I'm not going to give my address
qué y yo mi dirección no se la voy a dar
to anyone, to anyone, much less in this environment,
a nadie a nadie y menos de este entorno
to anyone okay And there was a dispute
a nadie vale Y ahí hubo una disputa
because, by balls, by balls, that I gave
porque por huevos por huevos que diera
the  address you know
la dirección sabes
and and nothing already in the end when they came to their
y y nada ya al final cuando entraron en
senses that it should be done by video call it
razón de que se hiciera por videollamada
turns out that instead of putting so that
resulta que en vez de poner para que lo
I do it by video call from here which
haga yo por videollamada desde aquí que
is normal luz welcome Thank you very much
es lo normal luz bienvenida Muchas
luz a kiss Already in itself instead
gracias luz un beso Ya de por sí en vez
of the normal thing is that you take and they put
de lo normal es que te cojas y te pongan
the webex here and I enter here 15 20
aquí el webex y yo entro aquí 15 20
minutes with the judge on the call and I do and
minutos con el juez en llamada y hago y
answer what he asks me okay
le contesto a lo que me pregunte vale
but they have requested that the video call
pero han solicitado que la videollamada
instead of here in the court of
sea en vez de aquí en el juzgado de
Seville party in Seville is suspended
Sevilla fiesta en Sevilla se suspende
without asking damn Ask me Ask me
sin preguntar [__] Pregúntame Pregúntame
and and I do it and we do it from here okay
y y me lo y lo hacemos desde aquí vale
but nobody has asked for the
pero nadie ha pedido que se suspenda el
trial to be suspended okay But anyway This is not this tet
juicio vale Pero bueno Esto no este tet
is not to announce that he has suspended the
no es para anunciar que ha suspendido el
trial much less if he has
juicio ni mucho menos si él la ha
suspended it on other occasions okay
suspendido en otras ocasiones vale en
anyway I suppose that the real reason for the
fin supongo que el motivo Real del
delay is that the opposing party must
retraso es que la parte contraria debe
be sleeping even less but not
estar durmiendo todavía menos pero no
precisely for musical enjoyment because
por disfrute musical precisamente pues
lately the dwarfs are growing the
últimamente le crecen los enanos lo
only thing I ask is that they stop delaying
único que pido es que dejen de retrasar
judicial cases for reasons such as
causas judiciales por motivos tales como
believing themselves to be the wolf of Wall Street
creerse el lobo de Wall Street
undergoing facial surgery
someterse a operaciones faciales
petting Thai otters or doing
acariciar nutrias tailandesas o hacer
pirouettes with taxation in
piruetas con la fiscalidad en
Spain, instrumentalizing
España instrumentalizar la
justice to create content is an lre
justicia para crear contenido es un lre
that affects
que afecta a que los organismos
judicial bodies being able to dedicate the
judiciales puedan dedicar tiempo
necessary time to other more
necesario a otros asuntos más
important matters and here I'm not going to
importantes y aquí ya yo no voy a entrar
tell you things that will be told
a contaros cosas que ya las contarán
Whoever wants to tell them, okay, but man, let's
Quién las quiera contar vale pero hombre
see, michu, there are some
a ver u michu hay un hay algunos
procedures that have not been known
procedimientos que no se han conocido
yet, there are some procedures that you
todavía hay algunos procedimientos que
say, it's not that they are clogging up
dices no es que están atascando la
Justice with nonsense, man, there are some
Justicia con tontería hombre hay algunos
procedures that have gone better and
procedimientos que han salido mejor y
others worse, no, and no, and no, and
otros peores no y no y no y no se han
nothing has been said yet, but well, what can I
dicho nada todavía pero bueno qué te
tell you, looking for the other's mouth, I mean, it's a desire to
digo buscando la boca del otro o sea es
[Music]
[Música]
e It's a desire for the
e Son son ganas de que ahora venga el
other to come and answer you and leave you in a bad light, and and the same
otro y te responda y te deje mal y y y
as always, no, I only want with
lo de siempre no yo Yo solo quiero con
my little letters and with and with my little dolls,
mis cartitas y con y con mis muñequitos
I don't want to mess with anyone, man, no,
yo no quiero meterme con nadie hombre no
my son, you're messing with the other one just to be
hijo mío te estás metiendo con el otro
honest, he doesn't invite
por la cara es que a él no le invita a
Fran to the sanctuary, but I'm letting's see,
Fran al santuario pero am a ver m Yo lo
I only found out once that he
yo solamente supe una vez que lo
suspended it  him because I had to
suspendió él porque yo tenía que
schedule myself no and I knew the reason okay And I
programarme no y supe el motivo vale Y
said it's a piece of work because the reason well, I'll
dije tiene tela porque el motivo bueno
comment on it, it will be commented on
ya ya lo comentaré ya ya se comentará
okay that's why when things come out they'll be
vale eso pues yo cuando salgan las cosas
commented on okay but
ya se Irán comentando vale pero
here you are looking for the other's mouth
aquí le estás buscando la boca al otro
here then don't tell me no I just want to
aquí luego no me digas no Yo solo quiero
be with my letter I don't know what
estar con mis cartita yo no sé qué
man isn't looking for him they want
hombre no le está buscando son ganas de
the other to come now and hit you do you
que el otro venga ahora y te pegue un
understand taking advantage of the
sasca me entiendes aprovechando la
virality of the moment because they have to
viralidad del momento porque tienen que
say something about cryptocurrencies if
decir algo de lo de las criptomonedas si
not they don't stay
no no se quedan
calm when they keep a low profile for a while they
tranquilos cuando están un tiempo con
come out calling attention they come out
bajo salen llamando la atención salen
calling attention when there is some
llamando la atención cuando hay alguna
funal Finally see if he is see
funal Dale por fin a ver si está a ver
if he is and it's like then don't say it because
si está y es como luego no digas porque
now for whatever reason the other comes out and
ahora por lo que sea el otro sale y te y
gets into a mess with you the other subject is going to be
se lía contigo el otro tema va a quedar
buried and everyone will be
enterrado y va a estar todo el mundo
waiting for the fight that you
pendiente de la pelea que tengáis los
two have you
dos
know but well it's there no
sabes pero bueno ahí queda no
eh Okay okay And apart from that it
eh Está bien está bien Y a parte que es
is not like that what what what he has
que no es así lo que lo que lo que ha
told no later Here we
contado no luego Aquí
have Javi but everything could have been
tenemos Javi pero todo se hubiera
avoided if  you would have gone well the
evitado si hubieras ido bueno que lo
logical thing would have been for them to put you on
lógico hubiera sido que te pongan aquí
a video call here and pin pan does it in 15
una videollamada y lo hace pin pan en 15
20 minutes and it would have been but what I
20 minutos y hubiera sido pero que te
tell you is that but the court does not
digo ya está pero que el juzgado no te
suspend a trial because you go to
suspende un juicio porque te vayas a
Thailand with francua that I understand that
Tailandia con francua que entiendo que
the cause will have to be justified
tendrá que estar justificada la causa
that you can say Hey look it is not
que tú puedes decir Oye mira es que me
good for me because I have a
viene mal porque tengo una operación de
health operation I know a thousand things is that I do not
salud yo que sé mil cosas es que no lo
know the others the others the other reasons
sé los otros los otros los otros motivos
no I do not
no
know or rather yes I have not even
No lo sé o sea s que ni siquiera he
spoken with Dallas about this issue to me
hablado con el Dallas de este tema a mí
the lawyer calls me he says man such a
me me llama el abogada me dice tío tal
day man such another day You know
día tío tal otro día Sabes
But well things are not like that when the
Pero bueno no son así las cosas cuando
forward goes Eh This is also fabric
vaya delantero Eh Esto es tela también
Eh This is also fabric
Eh Esto es tela también
eh the thing about the dwarves and the thing about Thailand
eh lo de los enanos y lo de Tailandia
were unnecessary no But well they
estuvieron de más no Pero bueno ellos de
have to say something about the cryptocurrencies
las criptomonedas tienen que decir algo
because they know all the content
porque ellos saben todos los contenidos
that Dallas uploads if Dallas has a
que sube Dallas si tiene Dallas una
controversy yes Win michu the other day they
polémica si Win michu el otro día me
sent me that commented
mandaron que comentó
on When I did the debate with mine He
en Cuando hice el debate con la mía Te
is looking for your mouth Javi I am
está buscando la boca a ti Javi Yo por
here in the media I can you  I can
aquí mediáticamente Te puedo te puedo
answer a couple of things but
contestar un par de cosillas pero yo por
here I'm going to tell you a little more A little more A
aquí poco más poco más le voy a decir a
little about me You're going to find a little
mí Poco de mí Poco va a encontrar
and well, let's see, you're going to find a little
e bueno a ver poco va a encontrar
publicly
públicamente
in the media, I
mediáticamente me
mean, he commented on the debate with me, I
refiero comentó sobre el debate con mía
don't remember what he wrote, I don't remember what he
no me acuerdo que es lo que puso no me
wrote but they
acuerdo que es lo que puso pero me lo
sent it to me and I said, [ __ ], the
mandaron que dije yo [__] al día
next day they sent me all the people who
siguiente me mandaron toda la gente que
started following me and
empezaron a seguir a mía y a ponerle
tweeting at me and it's like [ __ ] I mean, whatever
tweet y es como [__] O sea ya puede
character can appear eh but it's
aparecer el personaje que sea eh pero es
like dude, no, I, I, he, for example, right
como tío Yo no yo yo él por ejemplo
now He's with the
ahora mismo Está con el rollo de las
letter thing and I'm no longer in that world like I'm not
carta y yo ya de ese mundo como no me
interested like I don't know, I don't
interesa como no sé no sé con quién
know who he collaborates with, I don't know what videos he makes, I don't know if he's
colabora no sé qué vídeos hace no sé si
doing well, I don't know if he's doing badly I
le va bien no sé si le va mal Yo
only know about him when there's gossip
solamente sé de él cuando hay salseo
but the one from Dallas and everything that is
pero el de Dallas y de todo lo que sea
the environment and such, they know everything and they
el entorno y tal lo saben todo y lo ven
all watch the entire
todos los directos
live broadcasts which is fine, you're within your
enteros que está bien que estás en tu
right, I mean if you're there
derecho o sea que si tú estás ahí con
wanting to fight and you want to get moving, okay, it
ganas de guerra y te quieres movida vale
's perfect, you're within your right.
em está perfecto tú estás en tu derecho
What happens is that it doesn't add up  then with the
Lo que pasa que no cuadra luego con el
story of me that we are calm with
relato de yo que estamos tranquilito con
my cards
mis cartas
and obviously there is also the thing about
y obviamente también está además lo de
the
las cirugías
facial surgeries Well, a
faciales Bueno pues a él le apareció un
good tweet appeared to him, tit appeared what a
buen tweet a él le apareció tetazo
dilanterosinimaginasion I remembered
dilanterosinimaginasion me he acordado
the mess forward saying that he
de la que lió delantero diciendo que él
rejected gossip because he was super
rechazaba el chisme porque estaba super
against gossip that you have to see how
en contra del chisme que hay que ver qué
disgusting the gossip channels are when he
asco los canales de salseo que cuando
started to deny gossip that like a
empezó a renegar de salseo que como
host man you have been and you were a great
[__] tío has sido y fuiste un gran
gossip channel I remembered the gin
canal de salseo me he acordado del gin
over okay that's good no truth that they
over vale que bueno no verad que me
threw me in the gameover because forward
tiraron en el gameover porque delantero
because it's like let's see listen to me
porque es como a ver escúchame
that the people applauded not because they
que la gente aplaudió no porque se lo
took it as advice no that Dylan the
tomó como un consejo no que El Dylan el
roar of the bag's guts out of need
rugido de tripas del bolsa por necesidad
for approval but not me but it's that
de aprobación pero yo no pero es que
roar of the guts I mean he won't have money
rugido de tripas O sea no tendrá dinero
forward 23000 dislikes s Yes or so this was it
delantero 23000 dislikes s Sí o sea esto
I ate a year's worth of followers
fue Me comí un año a los seguidores
coming Oh is that you made a video
viniendo Ay es que le hiciste un vídeo
to Dylan I don't forgive you yet I don't
al Dylan no te lo perdono todavía no te
forgive you for the video  what did you do to him Like what
perdono el vídeo que le hiciste Como qué
video did I make man I gave him a critique
vídeo le hice tío le hice una crítica
comparing one thing to another and stuff like that
comparando una cosa con otra y cosas así
come on, he talked about [ __ ] great I'm not
vamos había hablado de [__] madre no os
going to put the whole video okay we
voy a poner el vídeo entero vale
could watch this whole video or like
podríamos ver este vídeo entero o como
any other people who have
cualquiera de a otra gente que le ha
dedicated videos to him too what happens is
dedicado vídeos también lo que pasa es
that in this video there are a couple of things
que en este vídeo hay un par de cosas
that I would like to discuss with you guys
que me gustaría comentar con ustedes
you fought with Porta over some [ __ ] stupid thing between
peleaste con Porta por una estupidez de
idiots of cco years you fought
[__] de [__] de cco años peleaste
with Porta over some [ __ ] stupid thing he
con Porta por una estupidez de [__]
says and porta threatened to
dice y el porta le amenazó con
smash his face in you fought with a
reventarle la cara peleaste con un
bunch of people over little
montón de personas por pequeñas
stupid things and the straw that broke the camel's back was
tonterías y la gota que rezó el vaso fue
making literally hour long videos about
hacerle literalmente videos de una hora
dros because he simply didn't want to
a dros porque simplemente no quería
talk to dyan He seriously has 200 views on
hablar con el dyan Tiene 200 views en
Twitch
Twitch en
but he had a lot of views
serio pero si tenía un montón de visitas
no [ __ ] he put Twitch if he has
no [__] se ha puesto el Twitch si tiene
balls
un cojón
No look two months 300,000 views on a
No mira dos meses 300,000 visitas a un
video
vídeo
Look no man he has good it's true he
Mira no hombre tiene bueno es verdad
has some weaker videos but
tiene algunos vídeos más flojitos pero
good but he has but he has a lot don't
bueno pero tiene pero tiene muchos no
be it he uploads very few videos no
sea es que sube muy pocos vídeos no Por
Why not I don't  I had heard from him again
qué no yo no había vuelto a saber de él
with you and El Rubius because he mentioned
contigo y al Rubius porque mencionó
about 3 seconds hon 7 seconds that he
sobre 3 segundos hón 7 segundos que te
mentioned you you did Almost more than half an hour
mencionó hiciste Casi más de media hora
of video in response to something of s
de video en responderle a una cosa de s
t is that he uploaded to all the mantras
t es que se subió a todos los mantras
dude he was a gossip channel and he uploaded
tío él fue un canal de chisme y se subió
to all the mantras of your followers
a todos los mantras de tus seguidores
are
son
children you have made a half hour video
niños has hecho un vídeo de media hora
with many ads all the mantras
con muchos anuncios todos los mantras
dude
tío
all all the mantras second in the
todos todos los mantras segundo en la
[ __ ] mother how he sucks dros
[__] madre cómo le chupa la [__] a dros
and El Rubius's [ __ ] eh Dilan How many videos did you
y al Rubius eh Dilan Cuántos vídeos le
dedicate to El Rubius dude have you seen the
dedicaste El Rubius tío habéis visto el
video that El Rubius uploaded the mother
vídeo que ha subido El Rubius la madre
who gave birth to me how jealous You have the seo
que me parió que envidia Tú has al seo
youtuber because you alluded to him with
youtuber porque te diste por aludido con
a video that he made that maybe it wasn't
un vídeo que hizo que a lo mejor no era
even for you a video that maybe it wasn't even for you he didn't mention you You simply took it as if he alluded to him and you made two videos 15 and 15 minutes half an hour for a mention Almost more than half an hour of video in response to something
hora de video en responderle a una cosa
of 7 seconds in the [ __ ] mother
de 7 segundos en la [__] madre
literally  how many minutes have you
literalmente cuántos minutos le has
dedicated to windy Gear for a mention of
dedicado a windy Gear por una mención de
how many 7 seconds how many minutes
cuánto de 7 segundos cuántos minutos le
have you dedicated to windy or how many videos and
has dedicado a windy o cuántos vídeos y
how many minutes have you dedicated to people
cuántos minutos le has dedicado a gente
like alator or jao Cabrera How many
como alator o a jao Cabrera Cuántos
videos my God How many videos have you
vídeos por Dios Cuántos vídeos le has he
made allo Cabrera Simply
todos hecho allo Cabrera Simplemente
because you felt like it watch out for these
porque te ha dado la gana ojo a estas
words that you dedicated to Nacho for the
palabras que le dedicaste a Nacho por lo
same reason what happens is that this guy
mismo lo que pasa es que este sujeto
continues making the same shitty
seguí haciendo las mismas bostas de
videos as always putting photographs
videos de siempre poniendo fotografías
of the tweets of people who are much more
de los tweets de gente que es mucho más
popular than him trying to keep
popular que él intentando poder mantener
his channel afloat And stop fighting
su canal a flote Y déjate andar peleando
like an idiot Concha his mother hon I
como [__] Concha su madre hón parecí
literally looked like a 5 year old boy fighting
literalmente un niño de 5 años peleando
over a candy You stole my candy concha
por un dulce Me robaste el dulce concha
your mother I'm going to have a debate with you
de tu madre te voy a hacer un debate
right now and for half an hour okay how
ahora mismo ya media hora está bien que
brutal brutal today's video of the Rubio
brutal brutal el vídeo de hoy del Rubio
has made me very envious intelligent but
me ha da mucha envidia inteligente pero
crazy keep it to yourself a bit the origin of your
loco guárdatela un poco el origen de tus
problems the origin of all the drama hon
problemas el origen de todo el drama hón
that there is around the review is like
que hay alrededor de la review es como
simply the fact that he can't
por simplemente el hecho de que no puede
take a  [ __ ] joke is it supposed to be that
tomar una [__] broma se supondría que
someone should take with humor that they
alguien se debería tomar con humor que
call him a pedophile, that they call him an aggressor and
le LL pedófilo que le llamen agresor y
all that stuff according to the good advice of the
esas movidas según el buen consejo del
Pope Dilan what do you want the acceptance of
Papa Dilan qué quieres la aceptación de
the people who do not accept you settle for
la gente que no te acepta conformate con
the acceptance of the people who see you
la aceptación de la gente que te ve
[ __ ] Upload content to them you have
huevón Súbele contenido a ellos tien
millions of people literally
millones de personas literalmente
thrown away by your problems, by
tiradas por problemas tuyos por
problems with people, by problems that you
problemas con gente por problemas que tú
create, by problems that you receive and that you pay attention to
creas por problemas que recibes y que tú
hon why do you fall like a p on
haces caso hón porque caes como un p en
the hook hon they literally tell you
el anzuelo hón literalmente te dicen así
like Hey [ __ ] and the other one,
como Oye dle huevón y el otro concha de
[ __ ] like grabbing the ground hon
su madre así como agarrando al suelo hón
and criticizing you making a
y criticándote haciendo un video de
half hour video wanting to debate with you
media hora queriendo debatir contigo
I say crazy relax a little relax
digo loco relájate un poco relájate
take things with bad humor
tómate las cosas con mal humor concha de
[ __ ] because this is YouTube
tu madre porque esto es YouTube
literally not one son of a [ __ ] has made
literalmente ni un hijo de [__] he hecho
a video without telling you I don't know rapist
un video sin decirte no sé violador
psychopath any [ __ ] Tell me the
psicópata cualquier [__] Dime la
definition of psychopath right no
definición de psicópata cierto ningún
[ __ ] had dedicated a video to you without
huevón te había dedicado un vídeo sin
accusing you of things will be this Dylan
acusarte de cosas será esteche Dylan
Because these  are your videos seo youtuber
Porque estos son tus vídeos seo youtuber
for me is known as
para mí es conocido como salseo de
Dallas salseo because I think it's one of the
Dallas porque creo que es uno de los
channels with the most videos dedicated to this [ __ ] idiot
canales con más videos dedicados a este
regarding the
energumeno de [__] con respecto al
breakup with his girlfriend with everything
quebre amoroso con su novia con todo lo
that has to do with his life Hello girl,
que tiene que ver con su vida Hola niña
I am D the review how old are you, did
soy soy D la review qué qué edad tienes
you like my book, are you 14 Look, it doesn't matter
te gustó mi libro tienes 14 Mira da da
if the police ask, you
lo mismo si la policía pregunta tú
were naked because you finished
estabas desnuda porque te terminaste de
showering and you just slipped and fell
bañar y justo te resbalaste y te caíste
on my penis, you come here as Digno to
en mi pene encima vienes aquí de Digno a
give someone lessons or like when
darle lecciones a alguien o como cuando
for example criticizing Cabrera there you
por ejemplo criticando allá Cabrera lo
pointed him out as if to say look, look how
señalaste como diciendo fíjate fíjate lo
shitty you are, the only one who
[__] que eres que con el único que te
talks to you is Dallas, that's why the only
habla Es con Dallas por eso con la única
person you had contact with who wasn't
persona que tuviste contacto que no sea
from your group of friends was Dallas, that's when you
de tu grupo de amigos fue con Dallas ahí
realize the awful kind of
te das cuenta de la clase nefasta de
youtuber that Sillo Cabrera is awful for
youtub que sillo Cabrera es nefasto por
hanging out with Dallas, how are you Dilan
juntarse con Dallas cómo eres tú Dilan
How many collaborations have you done with El
Cuántas colaboraciones has hecho con el
Demente, have you literally done a
Demente literalmente has hecho un
few collaborations anyway, it's the same
cuantas de colaboraciones en fin es lo
old thing, a little bit, it's not the same  always
de siempre un poco no es lo de siempre
a little but oh well there's nothing
un poco pero bueno que no tiene nada de
wrong with it right In the end let
malo no Al fin y al cabo que se las
the conas manage no and now if Dalas
apañe el conas no y y ahora si Dalas le
says something to him he answers well he manages it
dice algo le responde pues te la apañe
but don't say later that you don't like it it's
pero no digas luego que no te gusta es
a bit the same as we were talking about
un poco lo mismo que estábamos hablando
before Win michu no don't say later that
antes de Win michu no no digas luego que
you're not into gossip that I don't know what that I don't
no te va el salseo que no sé qué que no
know how much dude that you're not into gossip you don't
sé cuánto tío que no te va el salseo no
want to mix because you want to
te quieres mezclar porque te quieres
hang out with the con The Main Stream no
juntar con los con Los Main Stream no
but then in the end to throw it at The one who
pero luego al final para tirarle Al que
is frowned upon
está mal visto
let's see what's up with Dallas no
no vamos a ver qué es lo del Dallas no
What's up with Dallas from utbh let's
Qué es lo del Dallas de utbh a
see what channel it was on What
ver en qué canal ha sido
channel was
En qué canal fue
cryptas this game was too
cryptas este game era demasiado
good What happened to the bald guy
bueno Qué ha pasado con el calvo
mmm What bald guy [ __ ] did he take This
mmm Con qué calvo [__] se llevó Esto
is what you're telling me he took
es lo que me estáis diciendo se llevó
300,000 and I'm to blame I'll keep
300.000 y yo soy el culpable Seguiré
working full time for pambi Hi guys
trabajando a full por pambi Hola chicos
I want to start First of all This
quiero comenzar Antes que nada Este
video saying is that I haven't finished
vídeo diciendo es que no he terminado
with pambi yet I still work
con pambi todavía sigo trabajando a
daily now I make less posts
diario ahora hago menos publicaciones
because you already know what happens  when I
porque ya sabéis lo que ocurre cuando
say that I'm going to do certain things that
digo que voy a hacer ciertas cosas que
There are certain bad actors who take
Hay ciertos malos actores que se
advantage of it to make their purchases and
aprovechan para hacer sus compras y sus
sales taking advantage of my announcements
ventas aprovechándose de mis anuncios ya
since the market although I do not control it,
que el mercado aunque yo no lo controle
many people are waiting to see
pues mucha gente está al pendiente a ver
what I say so they can manipulate
qué digo yo para así poder manipular
the convenience price, which is why
ellos el precio de conveniencia con lo
some of the things that are going to be
cual algunas de las cosas que van a
happening that are going to be
estar ocurriendo que van a estar
happening I have to be more secretive when it comes to
ocurriendo tengo que ser más secreto a
when How Where and
la hora de cuando Cómo En qué lugar y
all that basically to not allow uh
todo eso básicamente para no permitir eh
garbage like the last time and what happened
basuras como la última vez y qué pasó la
last time Well as I told you we made
última vez Bueno como ya os dije hicimos
history and we would have gone to 30
historia y nos habríamos ido a los 30
cents a paní without exaggerating if
céntimos el paní sin exagerar si no
what happened had not happened and that was
hubiese pasado lo que pasó y que fueron
Basically sales in an
Pues básicamente ventas de forma
enormous way the day of the news that I said
descomunal el día de la noticia que dije
that we had listed, no
que nos habíamos listado jamás ninguna
meme Coin created by absolutely no one has ever
meme Coin creada por absolutamente nadie
been listed on a tier 2 exchange in
se ha listado un exchange de tier 2 en
just 5 days, much less had a
solo 5 días ni mucho menos tuvo un
growth of 1 million and Med by.  not
crecimiento del 1 millón y Med por. ni
even close to a mem Coin from
mucho menos una mem Coin de
absolutely nobody the developer 300
absolutamente nadie el desarrollado 300
pacos or in this case the creator who is
pacos o en este caso el creador que soy
me He has earned absolutely zero not only has he
yo Ha ganado absolutamente cero no solo
earned absolutely zero but on top of that he
ha ganado absolutamente cero sino encima
ended up in losses and honestly I was
termino en pérdidas y sinceramente fui
totally stupid because I should have
totalmente estúpido porque tendría que
taken profits because I could have
haber sacado beneficios porque sí podría
counteracted red candles
haber contr contrarrestado velas rojas
but I didn't it was all wild I said it
pero no lo hice fue todo salvaje lo dije
from the beginning everything is wild I don't
desde el principio todo es salvaje yo no
control anything I don't know what's going to happen I do
controlo nada No sé lo que va a ocurrir
n't know where the pyramid is going to go the
no sé a dónde va a llegar piramidal la
mem Coin is going to be in a
mem Coin va a estar en mercado
totally wild market I'm not going to be
totalmente salvaje yo no voy a estar
controlling the market at the mem Coin the
controlando el mercado a la mem Coin los
tokens are going to be burned I'm not going to
tokens van a ser quemados yo no voy a
control the tokens of n that the candle
controlar los tokens de n que la vela
was 30% heavier than it should have
fuese un 30% más heavy de lo que Tendría
been and you'll say how does Dallas know this
que haber sido y diréis cómo sabe esta
information Well well Apparently
información Dallas Pues bueno Al parecer
he told a certain person or
él se lo contó a cierta persona o
certain people in plural who then
ciertas personas en plural que luego
these people Well for stealing everything at
estas personas Pues por robarlo todo de
once and leaving people
golpe y dejar a la gente en
absolutely broke and such I
absolutamente pelan sdo y tal te
appreciate your honesty what I didn't know
agradezco la honestidad lo que no sabía
is that he was going to
es que iba a
00000 the day of the launch And the
00000 el día del lanzamiento Y la
truth is Let's see this is how the market is
verdad A ver así es el mercado
logically But there was liquidity to
lógicamente Pero había liquidez para
withdraw 300,000 bucks on the day of the
sacar 300.000 pavos el día del
launch It's that I don't have any captures
lanzamiento Es que no tengo captura
man It would be to look at it because of
ninguna tío Sería para mirarlo porque de
liquidity Here I have it open
liquidez Aquí tengo yo abierto
now right now liquidity
ahora ahora mismo de
right now liquidity has
liquidez ahora mismo de liquidez ha
dropped eh Now there are
bajado eh Ahora hay
235,000 on the day of the
235.000 en el día de la
sale is that I don't know there are people 700 800,000
venta es que no sé hay gente 700 800.000
I think he came to see it at the
yo creo que llegó a ver en el en el pico
maximum peak eh but we're talking
máximo eh pero es que estamos hablando
about a matter of
de cuestión de de
minutes it's his money I can't blame him
minutos es su dinero no le puedo culpar
because at the end of the day that's how
porque a fin de cuentas es como funciona
the market works it's not people of
el mercado no es de las personas de
disgusting snipers hyper trolls from the
snipers asquerosos hiper trolls del
beginning that I would have bought and I
principio que yo sí Hubiera comprado y
see that there is clear it's that Marciano I
me veo que hay claro es que Marciano yo
don't know who said it I don't know if it was
no sé quién lo dijo Yo no sé si era
true or a lie I think you put it to me
verdad o era mentira creo que me lo
here in the chat that night
pusisteis aquí en el chat aquella noche
that we were talking and watching the video
que estuvimos hablando y viendo el vídeo
of Marciano
de marciano
eh that he had put in 100000  turkeys I do
eh que le había metido 100000 pavos eso
n't know if that's true or false then
no sé si es verdad o mentira entonces
Of course if you've put in 100,000 turkeys at
Claro si le has metido 100000 pavos en
that moment when you start multiplying I don't know I don't know
ese momento que empiezas a multiplicar
how much Of course it's normal
no sé no sé cuánto Claro que es normal
that you take it out
que lo
he hasn't released a video
saques él no ha sacado vídeo
no
no
no the last video was c 5co
no el último vídeo fue hace c hace 5co
days ago it exploded The whole truth this was the one we
días explotó Toda la verdad este fue el
saw it will be true
vimos será verdad
man those are the most malicious there are
tío eso sí que son los más maliciosos
But honestly it does make me
que hay Pero sinceramente sí que me da
quite angry that there are people telling me
bastante rabia que haya gente diciéndome
that I made a rpol which basically
que yo me marqué un rpol que básicamente
means to make it go up and then
significa hacer que suba para luego
steal it all at once and leave people
robarlo todo de golpe y dejar a la gente
at absolutely zero and it bothers me quite a
en absolutamente cero y me molesta
bit that eh this youtuber who has also
bastante que eh este youtuber que encima
spent his time criticizing me fully and
se la ha pasado criticándome a full y
presiding for a long time you
presidiendo durante un montón de tiempo
specifically take advantage of this moment
aprovechas específicamente este momento
to sell 0000,000 And make the candle
para vender 0000,000 Y hacer que la vela
30% heavier than it Should have
fuese un 30% más heavy de lo que Tendría
been and you will say how does this
que haber sido y diréis cómo sa esta
information come out Dallas Well well Apparently
información Dallas Pues bueno Al parecer
he told a certain person or
él se lo contó a cierta persona o
certain people in plural that then
ciertas personas en plural que luego
these people well end up getting
estas personas pues termina llegándome
the information to me in the end  because it
la información al final porque es ocurre
always happens within the topic of
siempre dentro del tema de los
influencers again I can't blame
influencers de nuevo No puedo culpar
because it's still their money it's still
porque no deja de ser su dinero no deja
the market but it bothers me
de ser el mercado pero me molesta
deeply that people dedicate themselves to
profundamente que la gente se dedique a
lying saying that I am ugly to
mentir diciendo que yo estáa fea a la
people when I was the only one here who
gente cuando yo aquí fui el único que se
dedicated myself to working like crazy losing
dedicó a trabajar como un loco perdiendo
years of life and a lot of days without
años de vida y un montonazo de días sin
any kind of sleep to make
ningún tipo de dormir para hacer que
something like this work to benefit my
algo así funcionase para beneficiar a mi
community basically and they accuse me
comunidad básicamente y me acusen a mí
of having extracted money from the project
de haber extraído dinero del proyecto
when this youtuber took 0000,000
cuando este youtuber se llevó 0000,000
from the project and also the most
del proyecto y además el momento más
critical moment of all he will accuse him of
crítico de todos le acusará a él de
making an r Bull will accuse him of
hacer un r Bull le acusará a él de
having dedicated himself to scamming people
haberse dedicado a estafar a la gente
because he was also promoting
porque él también estuvo promocionando
Pico on his channel and he is making a
la Pico en su canal y está haciendo
tutorial but the thing is that he can't be seen
tutorial pero es que él no le puen a ver
there
ahí
here I don't know at what moment he sold
aquí yo no sé en qué momento vendió
Martian Is this like this or not I think he will
marciano Esto es así o no Yo creo que él
say it okay but Marc can't buy
lo dirá vale pero Marc no puede comprar
and sell whatever he wants the currency
y vender lo que le de la gana la moneda
is not his the problem is that you
no es suya el problema está en que tú
being
siendo
yours you sell supposedly causing a
tuya vendas provocando supuestamente una
fall
caída
okay it's useless  nor nor does it matter this
vale no sirve ni ni da igual este
argument is worth it, I mean Marciano, you
argumento vale o sea Marciano no se le
can't accuse him of
puede acusar absolutamente De
anything, of how to buy it and all that, in
nada de cómo comprarla y todo eso de
fact, his dick is not his balls, no, no,
hecho su [__] no hle sus [__] no no
obviously they're not going to say
evidentemente a él no le van a decir
anything to him because even if he made
nada porque aunque él se haya sacado 300
300,000 in profit, well at the end of the day
000 de beneficio Pues a fin de cuentas
he's not the hated figure and despite the fact
él no es la figura odiada y a pesar de
that I don't like the guy because of the attacks he
que el tipo me caiga mal por los ataques
made against me previously, well, I have to
que me hizo anteriormente pues tengo que
be fair and I'm honest. That's how the
ser justo y soy honesto Así es el
market is, everyone understood its risks and at
mercado todos entendían sus riesgos y a
the end of the day, [ __ ] of course it's good
fin de cuentas [__] claro es que bien
for him, let's see, he's put his
por él a ver él a ver ha metido su
money in, mm from the same ignorance
dinero mm desde el mismo desconocimiento
that any of us could have, not a
que podríamos tener cualquiera no un
viral topic commenting on it. No, he did his
tema viral comentándolo No él hizo su
analysis, I understand that since I don't know if he's a
análisis entiendo que como no sé si es
very expert, not in cryptocurrency, but he does
muy experto no en criptomoneda pero si
have a channel that's dedicated to that, I
tiene un canal que va dedicado a eso
understand that well, he does consider himself an
entiendo que bueno sí se considera
expert, no, he does
experto no eh
n't have any kind of
no tiene ningún tipo de información
privileged information, you know, the one that's being
privilegiada sabes la que se está
made public, not him
haciendo pública no el dala
constantly giving it away. Well, I'm going to take this out, I'm going to take
constantemente Pues voy a sacar esto voy
out the
a sacar lo
other thing that's not even relevant, but the
otro que no es relevante siquiera pero
fact is that I don't only think
es que de hecho yo no pienso solamente
about  that Marciano sold 300,000 means
en que Marciano haya vendido 300.000 es
that there will be hundreds of people who will have
que habrá cientos de personas que habrán
sold a lot of money Look, even if the
vendido mucho dinero Mira aunque la
liquidity is, for example, right
liquidez sea por ejemplo en estos
now there is
momento hay
236,000 of liquidity, okay, it's not 20,000, it
236,000 de liquidez vale no son 20000 no
's not 230,000 dollars that are not moving
son 230.000 dólares que no se muevan
but there are people who are taking out, are
sino que hay gente que está sacando está
selling. I mean, throughout the day,
vendiendo O sea a lo largo del día no
200,000 euros don't pass around in the middle
pasan 200,000 eur por ahí en medio a lo
throughout the day between buying, selling, buying
largo del día entre que compran vende
more, selling more,
compran más venden más compran más
buying more, selling more, we're talking about thousands of
venden más estamos hablando de miles de
people, I don't understand that
personas no yo entiendo que se mueven
millions are surely moved every
millones seguramente al
day, I don't know, I understand then, eh, there are
día no lo sé entiendo entonces eh Hay
many people who will have sold,
mucha gente que que habrá vendido
surely like Marciano and will have taken
seguramente en plan Marciano y habrá
out a lot of money, surely it was
sacado muchísimo dinero seguro pues era
his money and money that he decided to
dinero de él y dinero que decidió
risk to see if it would work and
arriesgar para ver si ía funcionar y
indeed it did work a
efectivamente que si le funcionó un
lot for him. Now the only thing I have for you, I
montón Ahora lo único que tengo para ti
know that you're watching this video, is
que sé que estás viendo Este vídeo es
that at least you thank me, eh,
que por lo menos me des las gracias eh
point number one, point number two, be
punto número uno punto número dos seas
honest because the information that I'm
sincero porque la información que estoy
saying here is real, you know that you
diciendo aquí es real tú sabes que
can show others  wallets and
puedes mostrar otras wallets y lo que
whatever but it would be nice if
sea pero Estaría bueno sinceramente que
you honestly told the truth you said it's true
dijeras la verdad dijeras es verdad fui
I was the one who was 30% of the cause of this drop
yo el 30% de la causa de esta bajada
because it was approximately a million
porque fueron aproximadamente un millón
dollars in drop that people sold
de dólares en bajada que la gente vendió
at the same time around a million
al mismo tiempo alrededor de un millón
dollars and he suddenly sold well
de dólares y él vendió de golpe pues
300,000 we all know that you can give me and
300,000 todos sabemos que puedes dame y
request 3 Give me something just pretend to say
petición 3 Dame algo amente fingir decir
no my other wallets my I don't know what my I don't
no mis otras wallets mi no sé qué mi no
know how many we all know how that works
sé cuántos todos sabemos cómo funciona
me This is information that has
eso yo Esta es información que me ha
come to me from people that you trust
llegado de gente en la que tú confías
maybe you should not have talked to all those
igual deberías no haberle con toda esa
people with this information because in the end it
gente esta información porque al final
ends up reaching me but at
me termina llegando a mí pero por lo
least it would be great if you explained to
menos estaría buenísimo que explicase a
people that I am not a scammer
la gente que yo no soy ningún estafador
that I did not mark any rpll and that
que yo no marqué ningún rpll y que
on top of that I was stupid but in order not to take
encima fui estúpido pero por no llevarme
a single dollar I Sao that I should never have done I
ni un solo dólar yo Sao que nunca tendía
should have
que haber hecho tendría que haberme
called money for this because money is
llado dinero para esto porque dinero es
what I have lacked afterwards to be able to
lo que me ha faltado después para poder
counteract these drops and always
contrarrestar esas bajadas y siempre
for all the exchanges you need
para todos los exchange hace falta
a lot a lot of money that
muchísimo muchísimo dinero que
obviously you cannot count on if you do not
obviamente no puedes contar con él si no
have it if not  you have won none of that I think
lo tienes si no has ganado nada de eso
I'm the only stupid one in the
creo que soy el único estúpido en la
history of the damn cryptos who
historia de las malditas criptos que
creates a crypto to not earn
crea una cripto para no ganar dinero de
real money it's incredible the level of
verdad es increíble el nivel de
stupidity that it reaches and despite
estupidez que alcanza a tener y a pesar
that I am the one who
de eso soy el que más acusaciones de
has probably taken the most accusations of scammer in
estafador se ha llevado probablemente en
the history of cryptos in the Hispanic World
la historia de criptos del Mundo Hispano
on top of it by scum that as I
encima por parte de gentuza que como ya
told you before garbage of
os dije anteriormente basura de
characters effects tremendous cowards
personajes efectos tremendos cobardes
who were dedicated to making Authentic
que se dedicaban a hacer Auténticos
rulls stealing all the money from their
rulls robándole todo el dinero a su
audience Like for example the garbage of
audiencia Como por ejemplo la basura de
that guy who doesn't even show his face
ese tipo que ni siquiera muestra la cara
and uses a photo made with ai and
y usa una foto hecha con ia y se hace
calls himself Trader and I think a couple of
Llamar Trader y creo hace un par de
years ago a Oh well the maveri but the
añitos un Ah bueno el maveri pero lo del
maveri thing the maveri is insane but let's
maveri lo del maveri es demencial pero a
see me, I am that I would not even be
ver yo yo es que yo es que ni me
offended by anything that maveri tells you, I
ofendería por nada que te diga el maveri
mean I consider it almost a meme, I
o sea yo lo considero ya casi un meme o
mean you guys what you have to
sea ustedes al maveri lo que tenéis que
name maveri is UFC simply Look at
ponerle es UFC simplemente Mira el tweet
maveri's tweet I sue the scammer give the review
maveri demando al estafador da la review
for  his millionaire scam with the pambi token
por su millonaria estafa con el token
Oh But there was
Ay Pero había
one that came to me before that
uno es que me ha salido antes uno que
said he's taken I don't know how many
decía se ha llevado no sé cuántos
million
millones de
dollars where was it maybe the
dólares dónde ha sido puede ser el
title of the
título del
video there was a t that said he's taken I don't
ví había un t que decía se ha llevado no
know how many
sé cuos
million okay
millones vale
and now we continue watching the video of
e ahora seguimos viendo el vídeo de
dala you know who I
dala sabéis quién me
feel like what party hom does
apetece qué fiesta hom te parece a ti
this seem casual to you dog Oh but hey girls TR
esto casual perro Ah pero Hola chicas TR
How hot you are
Qué ricas están
Oh but she's with a friend I was going to
Ah pero está con amiga iba a
invite her
invitarla
[Music]
[Música]
character but hey there were them She's
personaje pero est las había Está De
Partying It's that today What is
Fiesta Es que hoy Qué es
Thursday invite her anyway no no no man
jueves invítale igual no no no hombre
But now I'm not going to start making
Pero eso ahora no me voy a poner hacer
content a UFC token that
contenido un token de la UFC que ni
wasn't even the slightest bit related
siquiera estaba relacionado lo más
to the UFC to basically
mínimo con la UFC para básicamente
steal around 200,000 from their
robarles alrededor de 200,000 a su
audience another garbage of characters that
audiencia otra basura de personajes que
need to clean their teeth one of
le faltan limpiarse los dientes algún
these days saying that I scam the
día de estos diciendo que yo estafa
audience while he was dedicated to
audiencia mientras él se dedicaba a
making garbage Like for example making
hacer basuras Como por ejemplo hacer
his followers lose tens of thousands
perder a sus seguidores decenas de miles
of dollars with his recommendations for
de dólares con sus recomendaciones para
investment in bitcoin and he lost them
inversión dentro de bitcoin y los perdió
live that this was one of the
encima en vivo que esto fue de las cosas
funniest things in the world and basically
más graciosas del mundo y básicamente
those who  they dedicate Who is that This
los que se dedican Quién es ese Este
last one mentioned Who is it Watch the
último que ha mencionado Quién es Ve el
video of Rubius with willam sm I've seen him I've
vídeo del Rubius con willam sm lo he
seen him jamal I've seen him with
visto lo he visto jamal lo he visto con
Lorena he's made us so envious
Lorena nos ha dado muchísima envidia El
Rubius has made us so
Rubius nos ha dado muchísima
envious so very very
envidia muchísima
very [ __ ] For me it was a dream to
muchísima [__] Para mí fue un sueño
see it from the stands come on Ruby already has
verlo desde la grada vamos el Ruby ya
several several videos with
lleva varios varios vídeos con el
William m who is he referring to with him
William m que a quién se refiere con el
with the thing that he made him lose
con lo de que le hizo perder en
live calling me scammed are the
directo llamarme estafados son los
typical sick ones Within this world they've
típicos enfermos Dentro de este mundillo
called me a scammer for releasing
que me han llamado estafador por sacar
a video game for releasing books
un videojuego por sacar libros
literally for releasing stardeos which by the
literalmente por sacar stardeos que por
way is coming out now I'll
cierto se viene el lanzamiento ahora ya
tell you Soon and well
os contaré Próximamente y bueno
basically they call me a scammer for
básicamente me llaman estafador por
absolutely anything at least in
absolutamente cualquier cosa al menos en
the previous things or I won a little bit
las cosas anteriores o gané un poquito
at least I didn't stay in the negative
por lo menos no me quedé en negativo
But with this one on top I'm in the
Pero con este encima Me quedado en
negative because doing things right yes
negativo porque hacer las cosas bien sí
what about gon now we'll see it two Javier
lo de gon ahora lo vemos dos Javier
always if this with you Even
siempre si esto con vosotros Incluso
from the first tutorial I made where I
esde el primer tutorial que hice donde
clearly said that the very first ones
dije claramente que los primerísimos
have more chances of winning and the
tienen más posibilidades de ganar y los
last ones can also win depending
últimos también pueden ganar dependiendo
exactly on where they enter where they
exactamente de dónde entren dónde
buy  And where do they sell? Likewise, the
compren Y dónde vendan Igualmente a
only person I never wanted to harm
quien único no quería perjudicar jamás
in my life is precisely my
en la vida es precisamente a mi
community, that's why I'm making a
comunidad por eso estoy elaborando una
list of the people who are in
lista con la gente que sí que esté en
losses to include them first and foremost
pérdidas para incluirle los primerísimos
in all the things we do. This doesn't
en todas las cosas que hagamos esto no
mean that I'm going to let Pambi die,
quiere decir que voy a dejar pambi morir
much less the day that I say guys I ca
ni mucho menos el día que yo diga chicos
n't do anything anymore I'll just
ya no puedo hacer nada nada más os lo
tell you but that day hasn't come I'm still
diré pero ese día no ha llegado sigo
working on this in fact in a little
trabajando en esto de hecho dentro de un
while after this video I have a
ratito después de este vídeo tengo una
meeting that looks very very very good
reunión que tiene muy muy muy buena
and as I've already told you I'm not going to
Pinta y como ya os he dicho no voy a
let this fall I'm not going to let this
dejar esto caer no voy a dejar que esto
die obviously I don't control the
muera evidentemente no controlo yo el
market I said it from the damn
mercado lo dije desde el maldito
beginning it's a wild market I don't
principio es mercado salvaje yo no
control it even the slightest bit But what I do
controlo ni lo más mínimo Pero lo que sí
control is my work my desire and the
controlo es mi trabajo mis ganas y las
things that I'm going to do with the
cosas que voy a hacer con el token de
Pambi token beyond even listing it on the
pambi más allá incluso de listar lo en
exchange that I reserve this information
exchange que esta información me la
because I'm not going to allow
reservo porque no voy a permitir que
what happened last time to happen and of course I do
ocurra lo de la última vez y desde luego
n't intend to give them advance notice so that
no pienso darles antelación para que
no one does any closed what I can
nadie haga ninguna cerrada lo que puedo
tell you 100% is that I'm not going to  stop
deciros 100% es que no voy a dejar de
working on it that's something that I
trabajar en ello eso es algo que sí que
can promise 100% you know that I'm
puedo promet al 100% sabéis que Estoy
fully committed to this and I'm going to
totalmente comprometido con esto y voy a
give the best best best of me no matter what
dar lo mejor mejor mejor de mí pase lo
happens and whatever it is you should know that we
que pase y sea lo que sea que sepáis que
already made history The token is not
ya hicimos historia El token no está
dead at all yet but Marciano
para nada muerto aún pero Marciano
then took everything or left some pi we can't
entonces sacó todo o dejó algo de pí no
know let's see what he
lo podemos saber vamos a ver qué
confirms
confirma
he's gigantic I think that while
él está gigantesco creo que mientras
I'm recording this video he's at 4
estoy grabando este ví está en 4
million market cap obviously it's not
millones de market cap obviamente no son
the 50 or 60 million that we reached
los 50 o 60 millones a los que llegamos
But hey 4 million is not bad at all I didn't
Pero oye 4 millones no está nada mal ni
even think that 4 million
siquiera pensaba que 4 millones de
market cap I have no [ __ ] idea
market cap yo no tengo ni [__] idea de
what that is Market cap Ah Market c
lo que es eso Market cap Ah Market c
could be Market capitalization at 3
puede ser capitalización de Mercado en 3
million at 3 and a half million at more than
millones en 3 millones y medio en más de
3 and a half million it is at the
3 millones y medio está en estos
moment this would reach 4 million at
momentos esto llegaría a 4 millones en
first to all of you who follow
un primer momento a todos los que seguís
holde pis I want to tell you that soon I'm
holde pis quiero deciros que prontito os
going to need you to do some
voy a necesitar para hacer algunas
things I can't give you more details at the
cositas noos puedo dar más detalles de
moment you know Why we have to
momento ya sabéis Por qué hay que
have everything maximum  secrecy but
tenerlo todo máximo secretismo pero me
I would like to record that very good things are coming for those who holdan pambi we do one thing very very very important we had a lot of people wanting to screw us up from the beginning we had a lot of riffraff trying to destroy this from the very beginning and we achieved this together in the
y esto lo conseguimos entre todos en
community putting memes
comunidad poniendo memes por todos
everywhere voting all at the same time and
sitios votando todos al mismo tiempo y
this has never been achieved by anyone in the
esto no ha conseguido jamás nadie en la
history of crypto because there is no
historia de las criptos porque no existe
community better than us man I
una comunidad mejor que nosotros tío Es
want to see here what
que quiero ver aquí lo que están
people are buying and selling right
comprando y están vendiendo la gente en
now but it won't let me see it if I
estos momentos pero no me deja verlo si
have it on this
lo tengo en este
monitor let's see It's that I don't know how to
monitor a ver Es que esto Tampoco sé yo
read this very well either let's see no you can't see it
leerlo muy bien a ver no no lo veis
with me because I understand that this
conmigo porque yo entiendo que esto
Look at this here you see it says
Mirad esto de aquí lo veis que pone
25121 if it says two com 5121 What does
25121 si pone dos com 5121 Qué significa
2.5 mean Because look these are $2 that someone just took out
2,5 Porque mira estos son $2 que alguien
200 bucks okay look
se acaba de sacar 200 pavitos vale mira
here there's another one who bought 100
aquí hay otro que ha comprado 100
bucks but of course this is someone
pavitos pero claro esto que es alguien
selling
vendiendo
or do people start buying a dollar and
ó se pone la gente a comprar un dólar y
selling $
vender $
uh no $500 no  they are because it says
dó no $500 no son porque pone
2.51 Of course 200 are not like these
2,51 Claro que 200 no son o sea Estos
are
son 6
6.35 spit in my mouth grandpa I have
35 escúpeme en la boca abuelo que tengo
set how disgusting [ __ ] look here there is a
set qué asco cabrón mira aquí hay una
person who has taken out
persona que ha sacado
1260 here there is another who has sold not
1260 aquí hay otra que ha vendido no
0.8 that me but what operations are what
0,8 que yo pero qué operaciones son qué
operations are people doing here
operaciones están haciendo la gente aquí
man look these are 2000 turkeys that
tío mira estos son 2000 pavitos que se
someone has taken out but the other day I got into
alguien pero el otro día yo me metí en
something that I could see How much they had
algo que podía ver Por cuánto había
bought and How much they had sold I don't
comprado y Por cuánto había vendido no
remember where we were
me acuerdo dónde lo estábamos
looking at it this page was not the other day I
viendo esta página no era el otro día yo
was looking at a page that showed
estaba viendo una página que se veía
how much people were buying and how much they were selling
cuánto compraba la gente y cuánto vendía
Look Ah no [ __ ] wait the red one the red
Mira Ah no [__] espera el rojo el rojo
is to sell the other one is to buy okay well
es vender el otro es comprar vale pues
here is someone who has bought 2000
aquí hay alguien que ha comprado 2000
turkeys right now eh 2000 turkeys has
pavitos ahora mismo eh 2000 pavitos ha
played eh
jugado eh
the green buy is it true look here
el verde comprar es verdad mira aquí
someone has taken out 700 turkeys but
alguien se ha sacado 700 pavitos pero
man here here there are people
tío aquí que aquí que hay gente
buying for 80 cents
comprando 80 céntimos en
seriously look here there is one who has bought
serio mira aquí hay uno que ha comprado
turkeys Look selling 10 eur 10 What for
pavitos Mira vendiendo 10 eur 10 Para
what are you selling $ man it
qué para qué vendes $ tío
all adds up but let's see what you're
todo suma pero vamos a ver que me estás
telling me man Look this one just
contando tío Mira este acaba de
bought another person just bought
comprar otra persona acaba de comprar
2000 turkeys but here's someone who
2000 pavitos pero aquí hay una que ha
bought
comprado
0.50 50 cents [ __ ] what he counts What it
0,50 50 céntimos cabrón lo que cuenta Lo
costs to be a
que cuesta cerse
member I
miembro Yo es que este mundo de las
don't know much about this world of crypto either I'll
cripto tampoco lo conozca mucho ya te
tell you for me it's a
digo para mí es un
casino I know that a lot of people on my discord
casino sé que mucha gente de mi discord
have won because even though they didn't sell
han ganado porque aunque no vendieron
everything they sold part of what
todo vendieron parte de lo que
they got and I know quite a few people
consiguieron y sé de bastantes personas
hao dozens of people who are
hao de decenas de personas que están
between 10,000 and 20,000 in
entre los 10,000 y los 20,000 de
profit having put in just a
beneficio habiendo puesto apenas unos
few hundred for all those people I'm
pocos cientos por toda esa gente me
sincerely happy for all the people in
alegro sinceramente por toda la gente de
my community who are not in profit Let's
mi comunidad que no est en ganancia A
see wait tesa let's see tesa says the
ver espérate tesa a ver dice tesa la
column no the other column are soles
columna no la otra columna son soles
price in dollars no me the other day I
precio en dólares no yo el otro día lo
was looking at it on a site and it showed what they were
estuve mirando en un sitio y te salía lo
selling for How much they bought it you
vendían A cuánto lo habían comprado
know and it was It was interesting  know it
sabes y era Era interesante saberlo
because we were seeing things that were
porque estábamos viendo cosas que eran
very crazy
muy locas
but it is in losses that you know That I
sino que esté en pérdidas que sepáis Que
repeat again those who have
vuelvo a repetir los que más hayáis
lost the most will be the first I remember
perdido seréis los primeros me acuerdo
one of the days there was a day I saw it in a
uno de los días hubo un día lo vi en un
Twitter thread there was a day that someone
hilo de Twitter hubo un día que alguien
sold I don't remember how much he
vendió yo no me acuerdo Por cuánto
bought it for but he sold
compró vale pero vendió
884,000 he dropped the price quite a bit
884.000 tiró para abajo bastante el
and bought
y compró
82 I mean he made a huge mistake because
82 o sea hizo una [__] tremenda porque
with commissions he had to pay I don't
con comisiones le salía a pagar No me
remember how it was I
acuerdo cómo fue
look for you to include in all the things that are to
miros que incluya en todas las cosas que
come because effectively I'm
van a venir porque efectivamente Toda
not going to leave all this experience alone
esta experiencia no la voy a dejar solo
here again I'm not finished
aquí de nuevo no he terminado todavía
with pambi yet But it would be stupid not to use
con pambi Pero sería estúpido no usar
this experience to make
esta experiencia para hacer proyectos
much better and much more solid projects from
mucho mejores y mucho más sólidos desde
the beginning and obviously that will
el principio y obviamente que va a
happen but when that happens
ocurrir pero cuando eso ocurra antes de
first of all I'm going to do everything
nada primero de todo voy a hacer todo lo
possible to get pambi back to
posible para hacer que pambi vuelva a
where it was so that's my
estar donde estaba así que ese es mi
message to my community I'm not going to
mensaje para mi comunidad no os voy a
let you down I'm going to keep working on
dejar tirados voy a seguir trabajando en
this And if one day I achieve the achievements
esto Y si algún día consigo los logros
that I want to achieve which is basically getting
que quiero conseguir que es básicamente
listed on binance or binance
lograrlo listar en binance o binance
Depending on if you like Oxford Cambridge
Depende si te gusta el Oxford Cambridge
I'll say  here I finished my work and if at the
diré aquí terminé mi trabajo y si al
same time I can't do anything and I find a
mismo tiempo no puedo hacer nada y me un
dead end I'll also be honest
callejón sin salida también seré sincero
and tell you guys I'm a [ __ ] dead end
y os diré chicos estoy un cjón sin
and I don't know what to do but
salida y no sé qué hacer pero esa
I'm not even considering that second possibility at the
segunda posibilidad ni me la planteo de
moment there are still many things to
momento hay muchas cosas todavía por
do and there is still a lot a lot to
hacer y todavía hay mucho mucho por
achieve then to end up talking about
lograr luego para terminar hablando de
scum who is dedicated to saying a lot of
gentuza que se dedica decir un montón de
barbarities about me there are scum like for
barbaridades de mí hay gentuza como por
example Sprint who literally
ejemplo el Sprint que literalmente se
dedicated himself to defending coscu's biolor
dedicaba a defender al biolor de coscu
like many other streamers who are
como muchos otros streamers que se están
dedicated to saying Oh what a
dedicando a decir Oh que daras muy
scammer and pointing at me without
estafador y señalándome con el dedo sin
any kind of evidence while at the same
ningún tipo de pruebas mientras al mismo
time they were dedicated to defending coscu
tiempo se dedicaban a defender a coscu
when the evidence of what he had done
cuando las pruebas de lo que había hecho
was evident then other characters who
era evidente luego otros personajes que
are not streamers and who are authentic
no son streamers y que son auténtica
garbage of people who have shown me
basura de personas que me han demostrado
throughout the Open it in dex crener
a lo largo de los Ábrelo en dex crener
Javi dex
Javi dex
deener
deener
pambi decene pambi
pambi decene pambi
okay Ah look it's true it's true Let's see
vale Ah mira es verdad es verdad A ver
I like to gossip I mean it's not for
me gusta cotillear O sea que no es por
any specific reason but because I like to
nada en concreto sino porque me gusta
gossip this let's see I'm going  let's see
cotillear esto a ver voy a ver
wait well And where and where can you see how much he
espérate bueno Y dónde y dónde se ve por
bought and
cuán compró y por
or where can you see how much he bought and
ó dónde se ve Por cuánto compró y Por
how much he
cuánto
sold That's not it
vendió Esa no
eh
es está eh
eh ta ta
eh ta ta
ta click on the wallet but that's not how I did it
ta pincha la cartera pero así no lo hice
click on the wallet but I'm not going to
pincha la cartera pero yo no me voy a
start looking at
poner ahora a ver
wallets now or rather the other day when I was watching it it
carteras o sea yo el otro día viéndolo
came out next to how much
me salía al lado Por cuánto había
a person had bought and next to
comprado una persona y al lado Por
how much they had sold and so on all the
cuánto había vendido y así todo el
time pum pum
tiempo pum pum
pum what I don't remember where it was
pum lo que no me acuerdo dónde era
okay years like this guy called
vale años como el tipo este que se llama
Sergio who you know as the
Sergio que lo conocéis como el tío
white guy who also started defending
blanco que también se puso a defender a
coscu disgustingly repulsive I'm glad
coscu asquerosamente repulsivo Me alegro
the event went well there
de que el evento le haya salido bien
were a lot of people who were trying to
hubo mucha Peña que estaba intentando
boycott a brutal
boicotear brutal campaña de de
lynching campaign towards that justifies that you
linchamiento hacia eso justifica que tú
based on the information that is available you
a partir de la información que hay te
make this tremendous movie that this
mones la tremenda película de que ese
kid is a sexual abuser is a viol
chaval es un abusador sexual es un viol
because you you feel like ruining
porque a ti a ti te apetece reventarle
the event trying you can see how you try to
el acto intentando se ve como intentas
manipulate them and coerce it becomes I'm
manipularlas y coaccionar se convierte
going to try to destroy this
voy a intentar destruir la vida de esta
person's life  who has done this and I am
persona que ha hecho esto y yo estoy
accusing him of this and there are Hundred of thousands
acusando de esto y están Cent de miles
of whistles basically repeating the same
de pitos básicamente repitiendo la misma
narrative that I say p this accusing this
narrativa que decí p este imputando este
guy there to me does this the storm would
chav ahí a m me hace esto la tormenta
go the helicopters with the music of
iría los helicópteros con la música de
Apocalypse the parishes of Andora
Apocalipsis las parroquias de andora
where I live to do toid and you have it
donde viveo para hacer toid y lo tienes
there as a gossip trying to feed on the
ahí de comidilla intentando alimentarse
hate that they throw at me from all sides
del hate que me lanzan por todos lados
disgusting garbage of truly
basura asquerosa de personajes de verdad
totally repulsive characters and nothing That is
totalmente repulsivo y nada Eso es
basically what is happening these
básicamente lo que está pasando estos
last days there I do not understand it in the
últimos días ahí no lo entiendo en la
stock market in companies with low liquidity
bolsa en empresas con baja liquidez
they make these microtransactions but with a
hacen esas microtransacciones pero con
high price to raise the
precio elevado para subir el precio
average price that is shown I have no [ __ ]
medio que se muestra no tengo ni [__]
idea working full time a bunch of
idea trabajando a full un montón de
disgusting rats who dedicated themselves to
ratas asquerosas que se dedicaron a
defending scammers rapists and
defender a estafadores violadores y
repulsive characters on the internet now you
personajes repulsivos de internet ahora
have them saying that I am the one who
los tienes diciendo que yo soy el que
caused the drop with
provocó la bajada con pruebas
literally zero evidence and also saying that I am
literalmente cero y diciendo también
going to jail as if I were the
queo ir a la cárcel como si yo fuese lo
same as the garbage pyramid scam that
mismo que la basura estafa piramidal que
was dedicated to promoting for example
se dedicó a promocionar por ejemplo
German or you go to know it is always
Germán o vete tú a saber es que siempre
invented  a new thing and it's always
se inventa una cosa nueva y Siempre es
the same garbage scum arguments
la misma Escoria de basura argumentos
without any kind of sense with these
sin ningún tipo de sentido con esta
people Javi you have the page in the
gentuza Javi tienes la página en el
group I as for Sergio it depends Honestly he's
grupo yo lo de Sergio dependi De verdad
thrown at me three times half
a mí se me ha tirado tres veces medio
as a joke but he throws it at me and they are things
con broma pero me la tira y son cosas
that I don't find funny man I don't remember what he
que no me hacen gracia tío no me acuerdo
threw at me but he threw it at me as
que fue lo que me tiró pero me tiró como
if I wasn't I don't know what I don't remember
que yo no era no sé lo que no me acuerdo
what it was but following a bit of the
cómo era pero siguiendo un poco las
nonsense that people tell me and I didn't find it funny
tonterías que me dice la gente y no me
man Because with him
hizo gracia tío Porque yo con él
no no I haven't told him that kind of things
no no le he dicho ese tipo de de cosas
on some occasions that I could have
en algunas ocasiones que se lo podía
told him and besides when they are not things
haber dicho y aparte cuando no son cosas
that are true man you know what I'm telling you
que son verdades tío sabes lo que te
eh Yes it was I think it was commenting on an
eh Sí fue creo que fue comentando un
extract of mine with delos no that
extracto mío con delos no que han sacado
the clowns from Twitter have taken out No no it's that
los payasitos de Twitter No no es que
look at Javi the delos is telling him
mira el Javi el delos le está diciendo
that he threw it and that he threw it eh
que lo ha tirado e que lo ha tirado eh
him with the Dallas the price with the
él con la el Dallas el precio con la
wallet and that and Javi is trying to make it
wallet y que y el Javi está intentando
by force be forocoche let's
que por [__] sea forocoche vamos a
see the one who said the one who said here
ver el de los dijo el de los dijo aquí
look first he throws it  forocoche and these
mira primero lo tira forocoche y esta
people come here to manage this boom and they
gente se pone aquí a manejar esto pum y
throw it
lo tiran más
even more okay without more forocoche throws it and
todavía vale sin más lo tira forocoche y
then first they throw it these sales
luego primero lo tiran las ventas estas
of forocoche was not what delo said
de forocoche no fue lo que dijo el delo
and then they finish throwing it or
y luego lo terminan de tirar o
or they throw it even more with the wale
o lo tiran más todavía ellos con la wale
Okay without more but my mine is not the
Vale sin más pero que yo mía no es la
cryptocurrency nor do I have anything with this
criptomoneda ni yo tengo nada con esta
cryptocurrency nor do I know anything about
criptomoneda ni ni sé nada de
cryptocurrencies in general I play like
criptomonedas en general yo juego como
the one who plays the slots to
el que echa las maquinitas a las
cryptocurrencies I have told you many
criptomonedas os lo he dicho ya muchas
times I do not say what I buy or what I
veces yo no digo ni lo que compro ni lo
sell never for the same okay but
que vendo nunca por lo mismo vale pero
I was It was a click that they took me out
que yo era Era un click que me sacaron
of context when you see the
de contexto cuando tú ves la entrevista
whole interview let's see I'm telling
entera vamos ver le estoy diciendo al
delo It's that I want to know have
delo Es que quiero saberlo lo han tirado
these people thrown it or have the others thrown it he
esta gente o lo han tirado los otros lo
threw it and the one from delo
ha tirado y me dijo el de lo lo ha
threw it this one and such And I said Okay but
tirado este y tal Y yo dije Bueno pero
start throwing this one no and then the
empieza tirando este no y luego los
others okay Well then they cut it as if
otros vale Bueno pues lo recortan como
I don't want it let's see man that mine
si yo no quiero vamos a ver tío que mía
is not that I don't care if the  dasas
no es que a mí me da igual si el dasas
has done something that cannot be done well I will
ha hecho algo que no se puede hacer pues
say time if something happens to him
ya lo diré el tiempo si si le pasa algo
or not We will see okay we will see but I
o no Ya se verá vale ya se verá pero yo
am not eh Neither defending nor not
no estoy eh Ni defendiendo ni no
defending I am almost
defendiendo estoy pasando casi de
tiptoeing around this issue because they are
puntilla con este tema porque son temas
very delicate issues because you find yourself in
muy delicados porque te encuentras en
a situation in which you cannot
una situación en la que no puedes
accuse someone of crimes nor do I
señalar a alguien de delitos ni tampoco
want to defend them because I also do not know if
quiero defenderlo porque tampoco sé si
what they have done is right or wrong
está bien o está mal lo que ha hecho
because I am seeing it I am commenting on it to
pues lo voy viendo lo voy comentando a
me what interests me most about
mí que a mí Lo que más me interesa de
all this gossip about the bitcoin bread is
todo este chises del pan bitcoin pues
this type of things that they are throwing
este tipo de cosas que se estén tirando
between them without more you understand let's see
entre ellos sin más me entiendes a ver
This is the move no That no that is this
Esto es la movida no Esa no esa es la
page Well look
página esta Pues
neither eh Oh look yes No it is not
mira tampoco eh Ah mira sí No tampoco es
dude price sol price dollars
tío precio sol precio dólares
and panis I mean I understand that
y panis o sea entiendo que
this guy bought
este compró
cents I do not understand let's see I understand
céntimos no lo entiendo a ver entiendo
that this guy bought
que este compró
cents and has taken out 00 is that right no this
céntimos y ha sacado 00 es así no este
is the price at which he buys it This is not it
es el precio al que lo compra Esto no es
either it does not matter dude it is really
tampoco da igual tío es de verdad
totally repulsive and nothing that
totalmente repulsivo y nada eso
basically what has been happening the
básicamente lo que está pasando los
last few days while I am  working
últimos días mientras estoy trabajando a
full time a bunch of disgusting rats who were
full un montón de ratas asquerosas que
dedicated to defending swindlers rapists
se dedicaban a defender a estafadores
but this guy, what happened with Coku,
violadores pero este tío lo de coku
man, what happened with Cocu, there's no way to
tío lo de cocu no hay manera de
justify it, I mean, I'm not even telling you that we have to
justificarlo o sea yo no te digo ni que
catch the notes or kick him off the
haya que [__] al notas ni echarlo de
internet or condemn him. For life,
internet ni condenarlo Ya de por vida
the kid can't work. What I'm
que el chaval no pueda trabajar yo lo
telling you is that I wouldn't put him as the main character
que te digo es que yo tampoco lo pondría
in such an
de main en un evento tan
important event. Okay Javi, if you don't understand,
importante vale Javi si no lo entiendes
leave him alone. No, no, I'll leave
déjalo por la paz no no si yo lo dejo Si
him alone. If I haven't said it, it didn't
yo no lo he dicho n a él no me ha
sit well with him. Some comment he
sentado bien Algún comentario que ha
made, but well, the day I
hecho pero bueno el día que me siente
really feel bad about a comment, then I'll
mal de verdad un comentario pues ya se
let him know. Don't worry, don't
lo haré saber no te preocupes no te
worry, it will be noticed. You know that I don't give a
preocupes que se notará sabéis que yo
damn, but it is true that
sudo de todo pero sí que es verdad que
man, in this sense, I, this
hombre que en este sentido yo esto esta
way, this impulse to defend Goku, I
manera este ímpetu de defender a Goku yo
don't, I don't understand it. I don't agree
no lo no lo entiendo No estoy de acuerdo
H that that kid is a
H de que ese chaval es un abusador
sexual abuser, it's a vi because you, you
sexual es un vi porque a ti a ti te
feel like ruining his act, trying, it's
apetece reventarle el acto intentando
clearly seen how you're trying to
claramente se ve como intentas
manipulate them.  and coerce lasas
manipularlas y coaccionar lasas se
becomes I'm going to try to destroy the
convierte en voy a intentar destruir la
life of this person who did this
vida de esta persona que ha hecho esto
I'm accusing of this and there are
yo estoy acusando de esto y están
hundreds of thousands of idiots basically
cientos de miles de panditos básicamente
repeating the same narrative that
repitiendo la misma narrativa que decía
Pao said, accusing these kids t
el Pao este imputando este chavalitos t
graes a and this makes me the
graes a y a mí me hac esto
only one, the only one of all these people who not
único único de toda esta gente que no
only has AB taken from us not a
solo nos ha llevado AB solamente ni un
single dollar but on top of that I've been left
solo dólar sino que encima Me he quedado
with losses and the scammer is me so they
en pérdidas y el estafador soy yo así
can act like clowns all these
pueden hacer payasos a todas estas
vermin are bothered by anything I do
sabandijas les molesta cualquier cosa
And you know what I'm not going to stop and I'm
que haga Y sabes qué no pienso parar y
not going to stop taking things out I don't think
no pienso dejar de sacar cosas no pienso
well around here maybe it's worth the Martian thing
bueno por aquí tal vale lo de marciano
I would love to know I would love to
Me encantaría saberlo Me encantaría
know
saberlo
uncle well Jack I'm not going to get into that he
tío bueno Jack yo no voy a entrar en eso
could have given his opinion I can imagine
pudo haber opinado Yo me imagino por lo
more or less where the shots are going
que más o menos por dónde Iran los tiros
what can I tell you eh
qué te digo eh
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
n n I'm not going to get into that for the moment
n n no voy a entrar en eso de momento
listen to me that
escúchame
Martian thing I would love to know
que lo de marciano Me encantaría saber
the details well
los detalles bien
man I would love to know well
tío me encantaría saberlo bien
man but out of curiosity Eh
tío pero por curiosidad Eh me dan mucho
these things make me very morbid they make me very morbid
morvo estas cosas me dan mucho morvo
this  kind of things Ah well Let's
este tipo de de cosas Ah bueno Vamos a
get into this mess right now yes yes yes yes
meternos ya en este fregado sí sí sí sí
let's get into this mess
vamos a meternos ya en este fregado
Don
Don
Juan what was his name
Juan cómo se llamaba
Perez what was his name n of his last name
Pérez cómo se llamaba n de apellido
Perez what was his name they always put him
Pérez cómo se llamaba siempre lo ponen
on
en
Twitter the
Twitter la
goat Don Juan Hernandez Hernandez is not
cabra Don Juan Hernández Hernández no es
[Music]
[Música]
man it hurts when I breathe like my
tío me duele cuando respiro como la
stomach but the abdomen around
barriga pero el abdomen alrededor
Hernandez
Hernández
is Juan Don Juan Don Juan better known
es Juan Don Juan Don Juan más conocido
Don Juan Sanchez better known as anug
Don Juan Sánchez más conocido como anug
our father okay our [ __ ]
nuestro padre vale nuestro puñetero
parents able to moderate the chat of yo
padres capaz de moderar el chat de yo
Juan and one of le enir
Juan y a una de le enir
okay one of the
vale a una del
eyeliner that why the [ __ ] is it called
eyeliner que por por qué [__] se llama
like that because it's not called a tail man I mean
así porque no se llama rabillo tío o sea
in my time the
en mi tiempo se llamaba rabillo a las
girls who wore a tail were called that's like that no
canis que se ponían es eso así no
eyeliner what the [ __ ] is that what you did I'm not
eyeliner qué [__] es eso has hecho no
going to explain it really I mean and
voy a explicarlo realmente o sea y me
Javier iira follows me Javier iira Javier iira
sigue Javier iira Javier iira Javier
I want you to make me look good with the
iira quiero que me saques guapo la
thumbnail Javi Make me look good with the [ __ ]
miniatura Javi Sácame guapo la [__]
thumbnail Let's see you [ __ ] walte Let's see you
miniatura A ver cabrón walte A ver
[ __ ] says I want him to make me look good
cabrón dice quiero que me saque guapo
thumbnail says Javi Make me look good with the
miniatura dice Javi Sácame guapo la
thumbnail it's like let's
miniatura es como a
see no me no  don't make a bad joke on me
ver no me no me hagas así un chiste malo
anu Take me out like that there's not going to be much
anu Sácame así listo no va haber mucho
gossip We have to talk about more
salseo Tenemos que hablar de temas más
important issues there's not going to be much gossip
importantes no va a haber mucho salseo
okay 12 minutes that you have summarized for me luare
vale 12 minutos que me ha resumi luare
like the president's wife is
como que la mujer del presidente está
Hey okay No okay waltel
Oye ya vale No ya vale waltel
waltel you have already done the ra with me three times
waltel me has hecho ya tres veces la ra
with with nu spectators [ __ ] I think I
con con nu espectadores cabrón Yo creo
heard we have already heard you
que escuchado ya te hemos escuchado
enter
entrar
a judicial process and things like that I don't
reí un proceso judicial y esas cosas no
really like to talk about my life It makes me feel like [ __ ]
me gusta mucho hablar de mi vida Me da
But well what do I know it's reached a
e Pero bueno yo que sé ha llegado a un
point chat anug our father all this that I won't
punto chat anug nuestro padre todo esto
say the least I mean I'm not
que ya o digo algo lo mínimo O sea no
going to explain my relationship in
voy a explicar mi relación en
depth because it's a [ __ ]
profundidad porque es que es una [__]
[ __ ] pz I mean what I'm going to say is I'm going to
sopla pz o sea lo que voy a decir es voy
get one thing out of the way which is that
a quitar una cosa de medio que es que yo
okay I haven't cheated on
vale no he puesto los cuernos
absolutely anyone and that
absolutamente nadie e
could be debated Cristian games a
podría debatirse eso Cristian games un
hug Cristian I love you thank you very much
abrazo Cristian Te quiero muchas gracias
welcome I received some
bienvenido me ha llegado hoy cierta
information today that could completely compromise
información que podría comprometer por
nug while I was with princessita
nug mientras que estaba con princesita
in fact it's that no no I mean I'm not a
de hecho es que no no O sea yo no
liar you're lying now I'm going to explain
mentiroso mientes ahora voy a explicar
a little  the timeline of what
un poco el timeline de lo que ha
happened is going to be 5 minutes and little
ocurrido van a ser 5 minutitos y poco
more, which is like nonsense, it's
más cosa que o sea es una tontería es
really nonsense, it's a soz in
una tontería de verdad es una soz de
fact, I'm surprised that from here, I mean, I've gone from
hecho me sorprende que de aquí o sea he
being, I've gone from being one of the
pasado de ser he pasado de ser de los
most serious on Twitter, incel. Oh, let them
más seros de Twitter incel Ay que me
praise me but not even like what happened with
alaben per y ni siquiera como lo de
losos de toche You don't remember anymore no no
losos de toche Ya no te acuerdas no no
no our idol now and you're going to tell it
no nuestro ídolo ahora y la vas a contar
No leonia, I'm not going to tell it, let's see
No leonia no lo voy a contar a ver
because because apart from that I don't have proof they
porque porque aparte no tengo pruebas me
came to me and told me apparently let's
han venido y me la han contado por lo
see what they told me is that he
visto a a ver lo que me han contado es
was there I don't remember what
que aú pues estuvo No me acuerdo qué
party it was, I don't know if I ah I would have to
fiesta era no sé si me ah lo tendría que
review it they told me okay and like
repasar me lo han contado vale e como
an event he was there with some friends I do
que un evento estuvo él con unos amigos
n't know if it was I don't know if it was a party or
no sé si era no sé si era una fiesta o
a club the gamer could be it could
una discoteca la gameri puede ser puede
be the gamer who then went to
fuera la gameri que luego se fue a casa
some friends' house with friends and friends
de unos colegas con colegas y colegas
kids and girls and
chiques y chicas y
boys and there there were girls and such
chicos y allí pues había chavalas y tal
no And he spoke to the girls and well I do
no Y él habló con las chavalas y bueno
n't know now they have to tell me more in
no sé ya me tienen que contar más en
depth  details no but
profundidad los detalles no pero por lo
apparently one of the girls that was there was a
visto una de las chavalas que había era
big follower of mine okay And then there was he was
muy seguidora mía vale Y entonces
forcing the role of
había estaba por ahí forzando el rol de
the boys okay And then an said Ah
la chavalería vale Y entonces an dijo Ah
yes Javi the bastard I don't know what well he didn't
sí el Javi el cabrón no sé qué bueno no
speak badly of me no the truth is they
hablo mal de mí no la verdad me han
told me that he spoke well
dicho que habló bien
okay but yes it is true that as if he
vale pero sí que es verdad que como que
asked n Oh you really like
a n le preguntaba Ah te gusta mucho el
Javi and then you'll know Who is
Javi y entonces sabrás Quién es
princessita no that Javi that video of
princesita no que Javi ese vídeo de
princessita I don't know what And then it is
princesita no sé qué Y entonces se
understood that of course I was asking him
entiende que claro Le estaba preguntando
if he knew who princessita was to know
si sabía quién era princesita para saber
if he could finish locating no but
si podía terminar de ubicar no pero
anyway These are all all very
bueno Estos son tod todo muy
speculations and We have to close that
especulaciones y Hay que cerrar esa
information We have to close that info
información Hay que cerrar esa info
truths that is another topic eh Now that
verdas eso es otro tema eh Ya ahora que
you Cancel Shameless now my
te Cancelar Sinvergüenza ya ya ya me
time has come I'm done I'm done with the
llegó el momento se me acab se me acabó
choyo dude I'm done with the [ __ ] choyo
el choyo tío se me acabó el [__] choyo
anyway let's proceed Because I want to
en fin vamos a proceder Porque quiero
get off topic a bit okay basically it
pasar un poco de tema vale básicamente
came out on Twitter because eh it has been
salido en Twitter porque eh se ha
discovered eh that I have had a
descubierto eh que yo he tenido una
relationship with princessita eh And well they have
relación con princesita eh Y pues han
gone out with many  things about without
salido con muchas cosas de que sin
fidelities and without moves I'm going to
fidelidades y de que sin movidas voy a
make a very quick outline eh
hacer una escaleta eh muy rápida vale
okay okay Yes it has happened eh but I have not
vale Sí ha ocurrido eh pero yo llevo sin
been in a romantic or
estar en una relación amorosa y
sentimental relationship for 8 months well
sentimental desde hace 8 meses bueno
seven months there has not been a
siete s meses no ha habido ninguna
breakup okay I mean there has not been any of
ruptura vale o sea no ha habido ninguna
course the dates that they
claro es que las fechas que a mí me
tell me when the g merg Can someone
dicen cuánd la g merg Alguien me puede
put me there when the g merg because
poner por ahí cuando la g merg porque
later I heard him say this live
luego lo escuché decir esto en directo
I was here in the chat he has not
yo estaba aquí en el chat no me ha
spoken to me now a couple of times eh of course I think
hablado a ahora un par de veces eh claro
the gameri I think it was like that
creo que la gameri creo que fue por ahí
no So maybe I was no longer
no Entonces a lo mejor que ya no estaba
with her a breakup I have had
con ella una ruptura yo no he tenido
nothing to do okay eh absolutely nothing to
nada que ver vale eh absolutamente nada
do during these eh 7 months with
que ver durante estos eh 7 meses con
any relationship eh during the
ninguna relación eh durante la relación
closed relationship that I have had I did not F other
cerrada que he tenido yo no me F a otras
people and that's the summary
personas e y ya está ese es el resumen
okay eh during the relationship
vale eh durante la relación pasaron
things happened we broke up because there are times in
cosas cortamos porque hay veces en la
life that no matter how much you like a
vida que por mucho que te guste una
person you cannot have a
persona no puedes tener una relación
romantic relationship eh long term a
sentimental eh a largo plazo una
relationship okay And after it ended
relación vale Y después de que terminó
I found out that they had  third
me enteré de que hubieron terceras
parties and I basically what I said
personas y yo básicamente lo que dije
Hey eh if you want to earn my trust
Oye eh si te quieres ganar mi confianza
and you want to come back then you'll have to do
y quieres volver pues tendrás que hacer
a series of things it didn't get to that
una serie de cosas no se llegó a tal
point and I've rebuilt my life That's it there's
punto y yo he rehecho mi vida Ya está es
no more I mean it's pretty
que no hay más o sea es bastante
simple I mean I ended the relationship I've
sencillo o sea terminado la relación yo
met a lot of people I've been with
he conocido a mucha gente he estado con
a lot of people the other person hasn't
muchísima gente la otra persona no ha
met my expectations and that's it I mean no I didn't
cumplido mis expectativas y ya está O
want to come back That's it I've
sea no no he querido volver Ya está he
made my life it's not a problem I mean
hecho mi vida no pasa nada o sea cada
everyone has the absolute capacity to
uno tiene la absoluta capacidad de
feel how they want and to feel that their
sentirse como quiera y de sentir que su
way of seeing things can be one way or
forma de ver las cosas puede ser una u
another that's why I'm not going to go into it I'm not going to
otra por eso no voy a entrar no voy a
talk about specific things because
hablar de cosas específicas porque que
in life each person sees
en la vida cada persona ve las
relationships Well based on their own prism and I do
relaciones Pues en base a su prisma y yo
n't need like I mean for me if I've
no necesito como o sea para mí si he
had Luck is a
tenido La suerte es una persona
deeply independent person and that's it
profundamente independiente y ya está o
I mean I don't know it's it It's not a problem It's just that
sea yo no sé ya está No pasa nada Es que
no there's not much more and he doesn't care what I
no no hay mucho más y se la pela yo que
know dude I mean no I don't know eh what else it's that
sé tío O sea no no sé eh qué más es que
there's nothing more really it's a [ __ ]
no hay nada más realmente es una [__]
nonsense I mean it's a relationship we've
tontería o sea es una relación hemos
been trying to get him
estado más tiempo como intentando volver
back longer than being in  a
a recuperarlo que estando en una
relationship like that is already I mean
relación así que ya está O sea no pasa
nothing is happening I hope she is okay I don't le no le I don't
nada espero que ella esté bien Yo no le
know I don't wish her anything luare
no le No sé no le deseo nada luare me
can you cut for Twitter the clip
puedes recortar para Twitter el clip
where I announced that Marta Riesco is going to
donde he anunciado que Marta riesco va a
be a collaborator on Sálvame please am Malo
ser colaboradora de sálvame porf am Malo
and that's it let her continue with her life, let it
e ya está que siga con su vida que le
go well for her with the psychologist, I have already rebuilt
vaya bien con el psicólogo yo ya rehecho
my life and that's it the [ __ ] goat eh look
mi vida y ya está la [__] cabra eh mira
what she said Look what she said and she was
lo que ha dicho Mirad lo que ha dicho y
so Pancho Look look look
se ha quedado tan Pancho Mira mira mira
eh I mean nothing is happening I hope she
eh o sea no pasa nada espero que ella
is okay I don't le no le s
esté bien Yo no le no le s
no the condition was that she voted for Pedro
no la condición era que votara a Pedro
Sánchez there is the breakup I mean it's what she
Sánchez ahí está la ruptura o sea es que
said I mean I don't know it's already
ha dicho o sea yo no sé ya está No pasa
nothing is happening It's that no there's not much more and she doesn't
nada Es que no no hay mucho más y se la
care what I know dude I mean no I don't know eh what
pela yo que sé tío O sea no no sé eh qué
else is it's that there is nothing more it's really
más es que no hay nada más realmente es
a [ __ ] nonsense I mean it's a relationship
una [__] tontería o sea es una relación
we have spent more time trying to get him
hemos estado más tiempo como intentando
back than being in a
volver a recuperarlo que estando en una
relationship so that's it I mean
relación así que ya está O sea no pasa
nothing is happening I hope she is okay I don't le no
nada espero que ella esté bien Yo no le
le I don't know I don't wish her anything bad  and that's
no le No sé no le deseo nada malo e ya
it, let her continue with her life, let it go
está que siga con su vida que le vaya
well with the psychologist, since it goes
bien con el psicólogo yo ya que le vaya
well with the psychologist, man, and she's going to give it up, eh, I
bien con el psicólogo tío y se la pela
mean, let it go well with the
eh o sea que le vaya bien con el
psychologist. Okay, and she's going to give it up, eh. There's one
psicólogo Vale y se la pela eh Hay una
thing. There's one thing that was like, Ah, I don't
cosa Hay una cosa que era como Ah no me
remember the exact words, but it says
acuerdo las palabras textuales pero dice
something like, no superior,
algo así como no superior periodo de
trial period, [ __ ] off, she's remade my life
prueba tomar por culo ha rehecho mi vida
and that's it. Well, this is another thing, I
y ya está y bueno Esto es otra cosa yo
'm not with anyone, okay. I don't know who
no estoy con nadie vale Yo no sé quién
told her that I'm with
le ha dicho a ella que que yo estoy con
someone romantically. I'm not in
alguien sentimentalmente yo no estoy en
a relationship right now, well, I meet up
una relación ahora mismo yo pues quedo
with people, I go here and there, I don't
con gente voy de aquí para allá yo que
know, I go out to party, I'm calm,
sé salgo de fiesta estoy tranquilo que
everyone. Well, I don't know, that's it, I mean, ready,
cada uno Pues no sé ya está o sea listo
well, well, that's it. Okay, you already have the
bien bien pu ya está Ale ya tenéis el
clip. This is the most I'm going to say, I'm not going to go
clip Esto es lo más que voy a decir no
into details. 3 minutes,
voy a entrar en detalles 3 minutos
man, Ofelia, 10 pieces of members,
hombre Ofelia 10 pedazos de miembros
heart. Thank you very much. Ricky, learn
corazón Muchísimas gracias Ricky aprende
completely. Ricky, eh, completely
completamente Ricky eh completamente
based on nug, learn from your father, nug.
basado a nug aprende de tu padre a nug
Ricky, it's that, I mean, blaring relationships in
Ricky es que o sea alar de relaciones en
public is nonsense, I mean, anyone.
público es una tontería o sea cualquiera
that there is having a relationship, you know that it is, it's
que haya tener una relación sabe que es
like super, like, things happen and
es como super en plan sea pasan cosas y
those things can be Ja inv Vita nu
esas cosas pueden ser Ja inv Vita nu me
has blocked me Well, I think we
tiene bloqueado Bueno creo que nos
have blocked each other more or
tenemos bloqueados mutuamente más o
less, but the thing is that explaining them is
menos pero es que explicarlas es una
stupid, I mean, that's it, I mean, I don't know, that's it
tontería o sea ya está o sea no sé ya
and I don't give a damn It's not a
está e me la suda Es que tampoco es
question either, ask, this topic we made
pregunta pregunta este tema lo hicimos
viral here, right? This topic has been
viral aquí verdad este tema ha sido
viral and it has been
viral y ha estado en
trending because we brought it up here at the
tendencia porque lo sacamos aquí en la
salsería, no question, eh,
salsería no pregunta eh pregunta
humble question, so much that I know without more, more than
humilde tanto yo que sé sin más más que
anything The only reason I clarified this
nada Lo único por lo que aclarado esto
because it's making me think that I have
porque se me está poniendo yo de que he
cheated on anyone in revenge, damn, I have not
puesto cuernos en venganza [__] yo no he
cheated on anyone in revenge, no
puesto cuernos en venganza a nadie ni de
way. After having ended the
coña Yo después de haber cerrado la
relationship in a process in which I
relación en un proceso en el que yo no
was not in any relationship, I have [ __ ]
estaba en ninguna relación he follado
with people Well, yeah, damn, and she too, I mean, that's
con gente Pues sí [__] y ella también o
life, no, it's already, I mean, I have been in
sea así es la vida no ya está o sea yo
communication at all times, it has
he tenido comunicación en todo momento
n't gone well, well, that's
no ha salido bien pues ya está así es la
life, what do you want me to tell you, I mean, am, are you
vida Qué quieres que te diga o sea
fine? Yes, yes, But why would I
am estás bien Sí sí Pero por qué iba a
be bad if I have gone through like three mourning periods,
estar mal si he pasado como tres lutos
it's that I don't care, I mean, I continue  with my
es que me da igual o sea yo sigo con mi
life dude I mean this is internet stuff it's already peeled he
vida tío o sea esto son cosas de
completely peels the [ __ ] eh I mean no no no you're
completamente al cabrón eh O sea no no
smart Oh what else is already by the way
s listo Ah qué más ya está por cierto
ugly eh incel kids who are
feote eh chavales incels que me estáis
listening to me about that thing that a
escuchando lo de que lo de que se ha un
Goat has cheated on him in revenge
Goat por poner los cuernos en venganza
supposedly
supuestamente
[ __ ] humble response you have
cabrón respuesta humilde te han
all reacted to utbh magnetic
reaccionando todos a utbh magnetica
all following the Great King of the
todos siguiendo al Gran Rey de las
salsería most related utbh
salsería más reacionado utbh
And who has defended utbh
Y a quién ha defendido utbh
listen to me don't start with your role
escúchame no empieces ya con tu papel
anu of no I'm not I'm not the goat for
anu de no no soy no soy la cabra por por
putting skin no no no no start with
poner cueros no no no no empieces ya con
your role of a I'm not very ugly very ugly that you
tu papel de a yo no muy feo muy feo que
tell me that I look at women to
me digáis que miro a las mujeres para
want to [ __ ] them no no no no
querer follármela no no no
worth it No don't be no don't reduce it
no vale No no seas no lo no lo reduzcas
to that don't be humble no no it's that no no do
a eso no seas humilde no no es que no no
n't reduce it to the simple not to
no lo reduzcas a a lo simple no a
Christopher welcome it's not that for
Christopher bienvenido no es que por
putting horn it's not for putting horn the
poner cuerno no es por poner cuerno la
move has been to fulfill the requirements of
jugada ha sido cumplir los requisitos de
the list of little princesses  cure you that
la lista de princesitas curarte esa
list is worth fulfilling the requirements
lista vale cumplir los requisitos
while well you pretended to
mientras que bueno te hacías pasar por
be socially equal
que era socialmente Igual
ideologically equal all that stuff
ideológicamente igual todo esos rollos
okay you eat the horns you eat the
vale te comes la cornamenta te comes la
horns You keep that up your sleeve
cornamenta Te guardas ese bajo la manga
and it's your card for when they catch you cheating
y es tu carta para cuando te pillen
I mean it's not
poniendo los cuernos O sea ya ya no es
because you cheated on them no no
porque tú los pongas los cuernos no no
the card is kept for you And if they catch you
la carta te la guarda Y si te pillan
cheating which may have been
poniendo los cuernos que puede haber
the last time okay here's
sido la última de las veces vale aquí
the card we're tied and maybe you
tienes la carta estamos empatados y a lo
're not even tied maybe there
mejor ni estás empatado ni [__] a lo
are many times that they haven't
mejor hay muchas veces que no te han
caught you no but you played a
pillado no pero le has hecho un gambito
queen's gambit but come on completely So
dama pero vamos completamente Así que
let go leave your humility and say it
Déjate deja la humildad y dilo
the [ __ ]
la [__]
goat bros respected I mean please do
cabra brones respetados o sea por favor
n't [ __ ] with me dude I mean I mean you're
no me jodáis tío o sea o sea tenéis
too fixated on sex it's when it
demasiada fijación con el sexo es cuando
's literally quite irrelevant dude I
es literalmente bastante irrelevante tío
mean I mean the only thing I'm going to say
o sea o sea yo lo único que voy a decir
in the face of this is have dignity if you're going to
de Cara a esto es tened dignidad si vais
be in a relationship don't let it be for
a estar en una relación que no sea por
lack of affection if you want to be with
falta de afecto si queres estar con
someone it's a [ __ ] Life is like that
alguien es una putada La vida es así
but there are times that no matter how much you
pero hay veces que por mucho que te
like a person you cannot develop
guste una persona no puedes desarrollar
a long term project a
un proyecto largo plazo un proyecto
serious project that's fine that's things
serio ya está eso está bien son cosas
that happen It's okay I mean there are times when it's
que pasan No pasa nada O sea hay veces
not the moment moment that one
que no es el momento momento que uno
is at one point and that others are at
está en un punto y que otros está en
another point that's fine and also the
otro punto eso está bien y también el
issue of infidelity [ __ ] Whatever I
tema de la infidelidad fucking Whatever
mean they've put the leather on Madonna I
o sea le han puesto los cueros a madona
mean people just let themselves be
O sea la gente simplemente se deja
carried away by their desires and and they have no
llevar por sus deseos y y no tiene
responsibility Well well these things
responsabilidad Pues bueno son cosas que
happen I mean no it's not what matters most to me
pasan O sea no no es lo que más me
more or less in half an hour I will
importa más o menos a la media hora Lu
do it obviously well well I know
haré evidentemente pues pues yo que sé
if it's happened to you you'll know that it feels
si os ha pasado sabréis que se siente
bad but And what else I don't know Life is like that
feo pero Y qué más no sé La vida es así
If you can't uh decide what happens and you ca
Si tú no puedes eh decidir qué ocurre y
n't worry about the things you can't control
de las cosas que no puedes controlar no
I'm not going to get
te puedes preocupar yo no voy a
frustrated by something that I can't
frustrarme por algo que no puedo
control I mean the same as me I know I
controlar o sea igual que yo que sé yo
feel that I have the discipline so that
siento que tengo la disciplina para que
if the situation has arisen it doesn't happen but I'm
si ha dado la situación no ocurra pero
not going to judge either I think that people
tampoco voy a juzgar creo que la gente
can change in my specific case well it has
puede cambiar en mi caso concreto pues
n't occurred before continuing with
no se ha dado la antes de continuar con
the goat okay
la cabra vale
[Music]
[Música]
m me  you're all following me on
m me me estáis siguiendo todos en
instagram we're going to reach 100 I'm
instagram vamos a llegar ya a los 100 se
choking on 100 man it's
me están atragantando los 100 tío me
happening to me like on Twitter man on
está pasando como en Twitter tío en
Twitter I'm choking on 100,000 man
Twitter se me atragantar los 100.000 tío
look at it carefully okay look at it carefully and
miradlo bien vale miradlo bien y
follow me on instagram damn more salty
seguirme en instagram [__] más salcito
What's that no more salty damn look at
Cómo que no más salcito [__] miradlo
everything well make sure okay boom eh [ __ ] there's only
todo bien aseguraros vale pum eh [__]
19,000 missing 18,000 and something
es que faltan 19.000 18000 y pico
man 18,000 and something man What's crazy eh I mean
tío 18000 y pico tío Qué locura eh o sea
the same day I saw Will smi he
el mismo día que vi a Will smi él por la
went to Real Madrid in the morning to I don't know what
mañana se fue al Real Madrid a no sé qué
Real Madrid and then he went to
del Real Madrid y luego se fue a
record with El Rubius your
a a grabar con El Rubius tú
situation so that I regain confidence
situación para que yo recupere confianza
well it's perfect I mean it's what's
pues ya está perfecto o sea es lo que
ready in the rest what do I know a
hay listo en el resto yo que sé una
relationship is a complicated process that you have to
relación es un proceso complicado en el
build and in which I
que hay que construir y en el que os
recommend that you never enter into a
recomiendo que nunca entréis en una
relationship because you think you're missing
relación porque penséis que os falta
something entering into a relationship because you
algo entrar en una relación porque de
really want to have a project there's nothing
verdad queréis tener un proyecto no hay
worse  relationship that the relationship that a
peor relación que la relación que un
man has to try to fill the
hombre tiene para intentar llenar la
lack of affection that he has for himself, I mean
falta de afecto que tiene por sí mismo o
that's something that I learned many
sea eso es algo que aprendí hace muchos
years ago and it's something that helps me in the
años y es algo que me ayuda a que en el
moment that I'm with someone
momento en el que yo estoy con alguien
in which maybe I can't
en el que a lo mejor no consigo
find what I need
encontrar lo que necesito
[ __ ] Jessie Thank you very much welcome
hostias Jessie Muchas gracias bienvenido
eh In a little while I have the
eh Dentro de poco tengo el concierto de
Vival concert not in two or three weeks
vival no dentro de dos o tres sem
manillas I can't leave true
manillas no me puedo ir la verdadera
emotional freedom comes from self-love
libertad emocional se da por el autoamor
like I love myself like I have an ego I don't care I
como yo me quiero como tengo ego me da
mean a lot of people can see me and they
igual o sea mucha gente me puede ver y
can say man this guy is ugly such That
puede decir tío este tío es un feo tal
's the key a dick a dick do
Esa es la clave una [__] una [__] eso
n't say that nobody don't listen to me take
que no lo diga nadie no escúchame tomas
note eh this this right now Take note
nota eh esto esto ahora mismo Tomar nota
Okay
Vale
and and learn no you can't say anything else
y y aprender no no se puede decir otra
Take note of these tips because they
cosa Tomar nota de estos consejos porque
are unique I don't need to [ __ ] because
son únicos Yo no necesito [__] porque
I'm handsome I have ego I have self-love I have
soy guapo tengo ego tengo amor propio
a project I have a goal I
Tengo un proyecto tengo un objetivo
have the Stream I have everything I
tengo el Stream tengo todo lo que
need So I can leave whenever
necesito Así que puedo irme cuando
I want I can come back Whenever I want I can
quiera puedo volver Cuando quiera puedo
do whatever I want I don't need to be
hacer lo que quiera no necesito estar en
anywhere for eh I don't know asking for love That's it
ningún sitio por eh No sé pidiendo amor
then I really recommend you
Ya está entonces de verdad os recomiendo
incels you need to have a few more
incels tenéis que tener un poco más de
friends you need to have
amigas tenéis que tener relaciones
normal relationships and probably with the passage of
normales y probablemente con el paso del
time you're going to understand that not everything is about
tiempo Vais a entender que no todo
[ __ ] and that not everything is about being
consiste en [__] y que no todo
up there okay I feel like a
consiste estan arriba vale tiendo que
lot of people try to
muchas personas intentan como
systematize not to say okay let's
sistematizar no decir bueno a ver vamos
see what I need to
a ver qué necesito yo para
[ __ ] and he's the new yados giving
[__] an es el nuevo yados dando
motivations he's the [ __ ]
motivaciones es la fucking
goo it's that to me he's parted I thought
goo es que a m me ha parcio me ha
my father right now he's
parecido mi padre en estos momentos me
seemed
ha parecido
brutal to me I don't see no the one on twit too noos
brutal no vea no la en twit también noos
but twi is very empty no every time I go in
pero twi muy vacío no cada vez que entro
these days to your to download whatever it's like
estos días a tu para Descargarme lo que
very look right now
sea está como muy mira ahora mismo Está
Juan guarnizo is there with 5000
Juan guarnizo con 5000
viewers Jordi maquiavelo with 127
espectadores Jordi maquiavelo con 127
viewers nter is that goat he's
espectadores nter es la cabra esa
always with
siempre está con
cco let's see chocas he has 9000
cco a ver el chocas el chocas tiene 9000
which I think is more or less
que creo que más o menos entrar en la
average I don't know if it has gone down a bit
media No no sé si habrá bajado un poco
Sprint 16 there are fewer viewers
Sprint 16 hay menos espectadores
no there are fewer viewers not on Twitch
no hay menos espectadores no en Twitch
not to [ __ ] I need to be handsome have an
no para [__] necesito ser guapo tener
ego like when I started this relationship
ego tal cuando yo empecé esta relación
I  I had 300 viewers, I was still paid around
yo tenía 300 viewers cobraba igual unos
400 euros a month and on top of that I didn't
400 eur al mes y encima y no los
pay them in. Remember when you said,
cotizaba Acuérdate que tú decías para
why the hell am I going to be self-employed if I earn
qué [__] me voy a ser autónomo si cobro
500 euros? I've been ugly and fat like
500 pavos he estado feo y gordo como una
a bastard, I've never
como un cabrón nunca en mi vida he
had a relationship of any kind in my life, not
tenido una relación de ningún tipo
because I had money, power, I was ugly and
porque tuviera dinero poder estaba feo y
fat like a bastard, I was notable or
gordo como un cabrón di nota o lo que
whatever, but because I have self-love, that's it,
sea sino porque tengo amor propio ya
really, a lot of people have
está de verdad mucha gente tiene
too much, eh, you were and I am, but I've
demasiada eh estabas y estoy pero he
lost 8 kilos, I'm, I'm on it, eh. Oh,
perdido 8 kil estoy estoy en ello eh Ah
Osa, it wasn't any explanations, it doesn't give
Osa era no queas explicaciones no da
explanations, it's more like
explicaciones es más bien un consejo de
life advice, I mean, I want to take advantage of this because
vida o sea quiero aprovechar esto ya que
a lot of people are going to come in to tell you
mucha gente va a entrar Para deciros
guys that you're neither more valid for
chavales que no sois ni más válidos por
[ __ ] more nor for [ __ ] less, that you
[__] más ni por [__] menos que no
're not more valid because eh, that you've been cheated on,
sois más válidos por eh que os hayan
that you're not more
puesto no los cuernos que no sois más
valid because you're more or less than this, I mean,
válidos por por ser más o menos que tal
Don Juan guys, eh, be with
o sea chavales Don Juan eh estad con
whoever loves you, don't be with anyone just
quien os quiera no estéis con nadie solo
because you feel empty because  you
porque os sintáis vacíos porque os
feel like you need your
sintáis que necesitáis que os rellenen
ego stuffed because you need to be with
el ego porque necesitáis estad con
yourself And then you'll have the
vosotros mismos Y entonces tendréis la
freedom to be with whoever you want not
libertad de estar con quien queráis no
our father kid our
nuestro padre chaval nuestro
father you're a worse captain for reaching a
padre eres peor capitán por llegar a un
nearby port you're a worse captain for
puerto cercano sois peor capitán por
trying to cross the Atlantic in a boat you
intentar cruzar el Atlántico en un bote
don't know how to handle So little by
que no sabéis manejar Entonces poco a
little [ __ ] I mean that's it that's the point
poco [__] O sea ya está ese es el punto
Okay
Vale
try what do you think you But look at him he doesn't give a damn eh I mean he's
intent qué creeréis que os Pero mira que
there
se la pela eh o sea es que está ahí
completely sweating about everything eh days It's like he
completamente sudando de todo eh dias Es
's at the point like
que como está en el punto como de
suddenly a lot of kids saying this
repente muchos chavales diciendo este
guy that he's super ugly and that he went to such and such it's
tío que es super feo y que se fue a tal
like [ __ ] Whatever it is that I don't give a
es como fucking Whatever es que me la
damn I mean I don't need other guys to
suda O sea yo no necesito que otros tíos
tell me that I'm a [ __ ] to
me digan que soy un follador para
feel good I mean I'm scared I mean I
sentirme bien o sea yo tengo miedo o sea
know what I do and what makes me
yo sé lo que hago y lo lo que me hace
feel good and what doesn't make me feel
sentir bien y lo que no me hace sentir
good I don't need there to be groups of
bien Yo no necesito que haya grupos de
guys that applaud me like monkeys because I
tíos que me aplaudan como monos porque
don't need to [ __ ] to feel like a
no necesito [__] para sentirme un tío
competent guy because I'm already a competent guy
competente pues ya soy un tío competente
[ __ ]  I mean, you may like me more or
[__] O sea me os puedo caer peor o
less because I'm a [ __ ] red or
mejor porque soy un rojo de [__] o
because you don't like my face or whatever
porque no os gusta mi cara o por lo que
but I have a pretty good life I
quiera pero tengo una vida bastante bien
have a pretty decent salary
hecha tengo un sueldo bastante decente
I have the ability to talk to whoever I
tengo la capacidad de hablar con quien
want I have I don't know I have a life
quiera tengo no sé tengo una vida hecha
and what I don't need is for them to applaud me
y lo que no necesito es que me aplaudan
for [ __ ] [ __ ] I mean and I don't need a
por [__] [__] o sea y no necesito una
woman to be okay with myself and I don't
mujer para estar bien conmigo mismo y no
need I don't know what I know I don't know that's it it's
necesito no sé yo que sé no sé ya está
like my point of all this ready Ready There it is
es como mi punto de todo esto listo
the plane stays No yes
Listo Ya está el avión se queda No sí
in fact we have a campaign in a
tenemos de hecho campaña dentro de un
couple of days Alé that's it I'm not going to
par de días Ale ya está no voy a
comment on anything else because the thing is that
comentar nada más porque es que las
internet relationships are my eh if I
relaciones internet son una mi eh si
have another relationship you won't
vuelvo a tener otra relación no os
enter because I'm not going to go out
entraréis porque no voy a volver a salir
with anyone again that is public and that
con nadie que sea público y que vaya
everything goes well okay I'm not going to give any more
todo bien vale no voy a dar más de
gossip because it's that it's that for what I
salseo porque es que es que para qué O
mean I don't know don't upload your life already upload it
sea no sé no suba tu vida ya me la subas
to me imagine I mean at this point I don't give a damn
a mí imagínate o sea en este punto es
dude already take out the the if I'm
que me me la pela tío ya sacad el el si
going to take out a video put the [ __ ]
me vo sacar vídeo ponedme bien la [__]
thumbnail right okay or  be if I get the [ __ ]
miniatura vale o sea si me sacar el [__]
if I get a video put the
si me sacar un vídeo ponedme bien la
thumbnail right dude So at least you
miniatura tío O sea que al menos pues
always take like my photos from Google
siempre cogéis como fotos mías de Google
dude and it's [ __ ] well and marked
tío y es una [__] bueno y marcado otra
something else eh my values ​​​​remain the
cosa eh mis valores siguen siendo
same Because I repeat that I if
iguales Porque yo os repito que yo si
being in a relationship almost one a if you
estar en una relación casi un a si
want to put this photo okay I give you
queréis poner esta foto vale os doy
permission to put This photo gives me the [ __ ]
permiso poner Esta foto me da la [__]
photo dude for the thumbnail is that he is the
foto tío para la miniatura es que es el
father of all Right now
padre de todos Ahora
when he went to see monkeys from
mismo cuando fue a ver monos de
Gibraltar they applauded him and praised him it's like this take
Gibraltar le aplaudieron y alabaron es
it handsome
así sácalo guapo
Javi [ __ ] monkeys [ __ ] the monkeys
Javi [__] monos [__] los monos
my photo well you can put the photo of me
foto mía pues podis poner la foto mía
with the H like this in a corner it goes hard
con el H así en una esquina va dura
you can put tip put an arrow and put
puedes poner tip pones una fcha y pones
The Little Princess and the terrorist and that's it
La Princesita y el terrorista y ya está
type you have a video that freaks out and gives us
tipo tienes vídeo que flipas y nos da
I put that monetize YouTube if I
pongo eso me monetizar YouTube si lo
put it no no if I put the little princess the
pongo no no si pongo la princesita el
terrorist is not going to monetize
terrorista es que no va a monetizar
not the thumbnail eh great to Pérez
no la miniatura eh grande a Pérez
thanks for the two months ready okay
gracias por los dos meses listo vale
chat you have dignity Not everything is being  with
chat tenés dignidad No todo es estar con
people and that's it man What more do you
gente y ya está tío Es que qué más
want me to tell you keep your
queréis que os diga ten cerca a tus
enemies close but your friends closer you
enemigos pero más cerca a tus amigos
never know when they could
nunca sabes cuando te podrían liar
leak you ah I have nothing to
filtraciones ah no tengo nada que
hide I mean Sid a
esconder o sea es que Sid una relación
very normal relationship is it is that I don't know or rather
muy normal sea es que no sé o sea
simply It's that I don't like to talk about
simplemente Es que no me gusta hablar de
these things But well I mean I make a
estas cosas Pero bueno o sea me gano la
living with this there are times when being a
vida con esto hay veces que siendo un
public figure well you have to talk I
personaje público pues tienes que hablar
was going not to talk but I say man they're
iba no hablar pero digo tío es que me me
going to ask me people are going to come they're
van a preguntar va a venir la gente me
going to kick my ass I say I talk that
van a darar por culo yo digo lo hablo
whoever it is I upload a [ __ ] video
que que quien sea subo un [__] vídeo la
people find out and leave me alone some
gente se entere y me dejen en paz de una
girl saying that she was talking to de
tía diciendo que estaba hablando con de
gref and and she was telling him if there
gref y y le decía que si en el campo
were going to be three balls on the field or I don't know what I mean what
iban a haber tres pelotas o no sé qué O
what what's going on I mean
sea qué qué qué está pasando O sea
save me for men man I mean for real I
sálvame para hombres tío o sea de verdad
mean this is for men no
o sea esto es para hombres fuera de
kidding eh but I've been watching
coñas eh pero he estado viendo lo del
this save me on Twitch and I don't understand
salvame este de Twitch t no me entero de
anything I mean no kidding I don't understand
nada o sea fuera de coñas no me entero
anything I mean he starts saying yes because
de nada o sea se pone a decir sí porque
the husband of I don't know who did why don't they
el marido de no sé quién hizo por qué no
talk about the anjos dude because why do
hablan lo del anjos tío porque por qué
n't they update because why don't they
no que se actualicen porque por no
talk about the thing about the thing about No my [ __ ]
hablan de lo de de lo de No mi [__]
father my [ __ ] father besides that's how it is
padre mi [__] padre además que es así
anu I mean I was these last
anu O sea yo estuve est estos últimos
two days paying less attention to the content
dos días atendiendo menos el contenido
of telesalseo than about sálvame and so on
de telesalseo de lo de sálvame y demás
because I was busy with yours which was
porque estaba liado con lo tuyo que era
the best [ __ ] gossip of this week dude I
el mejor [__] salseo de esta semana tío
mean it's been the gossip of this
o sea es que ha sido el salseo de esta
week there's no more I don't know who and I don't know
semana no hay más No sé quién y no sé
how much dude I better find out no let's
cuánto tío que yo me entere mejor no a
see yeah To a certain extent Yes I don't know
ver sí Hasta cierto punto Sí yo que sé
there's a sálvame on Twitch yes it's sálvame it
hay un sálvame en Twitch sí es sálvame
's literally sálvame What's the
es literalmente sálvame Cómo se llama el
channel called eh that they haban What's the
canal eh que haban Cómo se llama el
channel called quicky quicky I don't know what no I mean
canal quicky quicky no sé qué no O sea
literally and I mean save me goat dude
literalmente e o sea salvame cabra tío
communicated if he says interest get out of here I
comunicado si te dice interes sal de vas
would think about it it's just a lot of fun I mean it
me lo pensaría es que es mucho cachondeo
makes me laugh okay that's what I
O sea me me hace gracia vale eso es lo
said at the beginning beginning said No
que decí al principio principio dijo No
no nobody has sold anything nobody has done
no nadie ha vendido nada nadie ha hecho
that  the price falls it is discovered that yes he
que caiga el precio se descubre que sí
says well let's see yes we sold but it was
dice bueno a ver sí vendimos pero fue
to scare the big holders and to
para asustar a los grandes poseedores y
control the price which is illegal
que controlar el precio Lo que es ilegal
But well okay I mean this is not I mean okay
Pero bueno okay O sea yo esto no O sea
uh another crime to the list okay
vale eh otro delito más a la lista vale
because controlling making
porque controlar hacer movimientos de
strategic market movements to manipulate the
mercado estratégicos para manipular el
price is a crime eh But well eh
precio es un delito eh Pero bueno eh
then he says well let's see you say that they
después dice bueno a ver decís que que
did it to make money and it's
lo han hecho para ganar dinero y es
because they had a super serious problem
porque ha tenido un problema super grave
in their life it's an outrage eh
en su vida es una barbaridad eh se va
this guy goes jumping salty jumping I think
saltar salando saltando este tío Yo creo
this is over if the CNM gets going they will
que esta es over si la cnm se pone se lo
load it in 20
cargan por 20
places I am that already Look at the best
sitios Yo es que ya Mira el millor
talking about this subject look here it is
hablando de ese tema mira aquí está
uploaded listen to me
subido que
the CNMV is from Spain only do
escúchame la cnmv es de España solamente
n't be if dasas does not live in Spain they
no sea si el dasas no vive en España
would have to report it
tendrían que denunciarlo
like if they consider that he has done illegal they
cóm si consideran que ha hecho ilegal
how I don't have the slightest idea how that would
cómo no tengo la más [__] idea de cómo
go the truth
iría eso la verdad
and you know what that about this I have some
e sabéis qué que sobre esto tengo yo una
big news But big big big like the like
gorda Pero gorda gorda gorda como la
the  better not know and we don't know how it will
a lo mejor no lo sabe y no sabemos cómo
feel about little princess
sentar sobre princesita
Yeah I mean I kept quiet and let him
Sí o sea me lo he callado y lo he dejado
finish talking
que termine de hablar
[Music]
[Música]
anud will be the new signing of Big
anud será el nuevo fichaje de gran
Brother say it already grandpa cacao 4 love
hermano suéltalo ya abuelo cacao 4 love
brother doesn't deserve it
hermano no se merece
no Let's see this is public surely
no A ver esto es público seguramente
There will be people who How good that by
Habrá gente que Que bueno que al
crossing here through this channel if you
cruzarse por aquí por este canal si
use this type of
utilizáis este tipo de
applications you have been able to find her
aplicaciones la habéis podido encontrar
an
an
ZZ anu Z zason Boy What are you talking about you
ZZ anu Z zason Boy De qué estás hablando
don't know anything about
no sabes nada de la
life do you know what
vida sabéis qué es
this is Ramón that
esto Ramón esa
busty but but that fit son of a
tetona pero pero eso fit hijo de la
[ __ ] I mean those bits I mean busty
grandísima [__] o sea esos bits o sea
there super
tetona ahí super
Random of course let's see this girl was
Random claro a ver esta chica estaba
doing a 3 hour live
haciendo un directo de 3 horas
crying while she was doing a
llorando mientras que hacía un directo
3 hour live Crying she was looking for
de 3 horas Llorando se estaba buscando
the she was looking for the the the theme she
la se estaba buscando el el el temilla
wasn't looking for the theme
no se estaba buscando el temilla por
somewhere it could be fake No no it's not fake it's not
ahí puede ser fake No no es fake no es
fake it's not fake it's not
fake no es fake no es
fake Ramón Today is the
fake Ramón Hoy es el
day we want the tinder profile of the
día queremos el perfil de tinder de la
goat anug that one that one that one is not
cabra anug ese ese ese no está al
available to
alcance de
everyone I want to feel your body jun it
todos quiero sentir tu cuerpo jun
's proven Karime  that it's real
está comprobado Karime que sea real
is not proven but apart from that it can't be
no está comprobado pero aparte eso no
falsified, not these profiles
puede falsificar no sea estos perfiles
like an identification and they
como una identificación y te lo
check it precisely for those things,
comprueban precisamente para esas cosas
no if I have two cups of tea it would be like a little
no si tengo dos tazas de té sería como
princess How great Gabrielo
princesita Qué grande gabrielo
Thank you very much Rey a big
Muchísimas gracias Rey un
kiss yes it can be
besote sí se puede
falsified it seems to me that this has a
falsificar me suena que esto tiene un
type of filter
tipo de filtro
[Music]
[Música]
yes it
sí que se
can So let's put the
puede Entonces vamos a ponerlo bien el
tweet right let's put the tweet right okay
tweet vamos a ponerlo bien el twit vale
while little princess was doing a
mientras princesita hacía un directo de
3 hour live crying because Anut was ignoring
3 horas llorando porque anut pasaba de
her there are people who have found this
ella hay gente que ha encontrado este
profile I think they verify your face I think that's
perfil creo que verifican tu rostro yo
precisely to
creo que que para precisamente para
avoid that because if not look at all the
evitar eso porque si no fíjate tdo el
fun I mean we're talking about
cachondeo o sea estamos hablando que
2024 we're not you know like in the
estamos en 2024 no estamos ya sabes como
past they would steal your identity
antiguamente que te robaban la identidad
on Facebook and nothing happened okay there are
en Facebook y no pasaba nada vale hay
people who have
gente que ha
found this Tinder profile it's not
encontrado este perfil de tinder no se
called No Tinder is not called
llama No tinder no se llama
this I love it I love the Boomers
esto Me encanta me encanta los Boomer
that I am eh Tinder is not called this the
que soy eh tinder no se llama esto la
goat boy the
cabra chaval la cabra
goat boy it's not Tinder So which one
chaval no es tinder Entonces cuál
is it is not Tinder So which one is it come on
es no es tinder Entonces cuál es venga
Oh but I'm not going to put  red [ __ ] [ __ ] is that what does it
Ah pero no voy a poner rojo [__] [__] es
matter tinder that red that I don't know
eso qué más da tinder que rojo que no sé
what I mean it's a tinder type app it doesn't matter Yeah sure I mean like it doesn't matter it's
qué o sea es una aplicación tipo tinder
understood
entiende
also an app Ah okay Yeah that
además una aplicación Ah vale Sí esa
app is going to eat my balls he
aplicación me va a comer los [__] que
talked bad about me once because he watched
habló mal de mí una vez porque se tragó
a video of
un vídeo de
the crazy coio
las locas del coio
that the Twitter account that is called
esa la cuenta de Twitter que se llama
crazy
locas del
coio tinder is to be Friends or
coio tinder es para para ser Amigos o
friends Sure well that's it
amigas Claro pues ya
dude Why does my stomach hurt
está tío Por qué me duele la barriga
But it also hurts
Pero además me duele
how can it be because because I did
es como puede ser porque porque he hecho
abs
abdomen
No what else What else What else What
No qué más Qué más Qué más Qué
else Ah the clear thing It's true that we did
más Ah lo de claro Es verdad que aller
n't see it yesterday dude in the end the Sprint thing
no lo vimos tío al final lo de Sprint
I was looking for a video because [ __ ] It's that
estuve buscando un vídeo porque [__] Es
these are childish things Look Spring is
que esto son niñerías Mira Spring es
doxed live does your
doxeado en directo te lo duele la
stomach hurt because you're too massaged handsome
barriga porque estás muy masado guapetón
stop doing so much exercise cacao 4
deja de hacer tanto ejercicio cacao 4
Love quo I've been watching a bit I've
Love quo me he puesto un poco a ver He
gained a bit of weight I understand that maybe I
engordado un poco entiendo que a lo
'll be a little stronger
mejor estaré un poquito más fuerte
too it can't be noticeable I'm
también no se me nota me lo estoy
noticing my forehead but let's see I'm
notando yo la frente pero a ver estoy
going  to the gym and such But I
yendo a gimnasio Y tal Pero
've been eating a lot these last few days
Estoy comiendo mucho estos últimos días
the truth and and I've gained a little weight I notice a
la verdad y y engordado un poco me noto
little fatter around the
un poco más gordo de
belly Sprint is doado live your
barriga Sprint es doado en directo tu
little sister won't be longer than a
hermanita pequeña no pasará de una
week what do you think Hi, we are odar you're going to
semana qué cre Hola somos odar vas a
pay to tell them But these from legón
pagar por decirles Pero estos de legón
odar are friends of the nauter FL and
odar son amigos de la nauter FL y esas
stuff man, I mean I know
cosas tío o sea
this I've already seen them chat with
se esto ya lo he visto yo chatear con
her and with Or him or whatever the [ __ ] is
ella y con O él o lo que [__] sea que
behind that account no and they're the
esté detrás de esa cuenta no y son los
same These are kids probably
mismos Estos son críos seguramente
trying Look, now she's getting
intentando Mira pues ahora está llamando
attention she's gotten a
la atención ha conseguido que ahora un
celebrity to dedicate 2 minutes of a
famoso le dedique 2 minutos de un
live stream to her these are the same ones who doxxed
directo estos son los mismo que doxearon
Dallas's sister do you remember
a la hermana del Dallas os acordáis la
Dallas's sister and I have a video
hermana del Dallas y yo tengo un vídeo
that I don't remember her name I do
pasa que no me acuerdo cómo se llamaba
n't
no me
remember it was on the main channel
acuerdo era en el canal principal
you I have a video on the
tú Yo tengo un vídeo en el canal
main channel in which it said that Chocos
principal que contaba que al chocas
had gone to their house
habían ido a su casa
to see but this was two or three years ago
a ver pero esto hace ya dos o tres años
and they're the same ones but it's that they start to
y son los mismos pero es que se ponen a
me they started sending me a lot of
mí se pusieron como a mandarme muchos
emails that you trust so I can con  an
email que fíate tú para que yo de con un
email you must be
email ya me tienes que estar haciendo
spamming me okay And it's to get Well look
spam vale Y es para conseguir Pues mira
two minutes in fact I remember that
dos minutitos de hecho me suena que
when I made the video they
cuando hice el vídeo me
talked to me I remember that when I made the
hablaron me suena que cuando hice el
video they talked to me
vídeo me hablaron
I remember
me acuerdo
man it will be more or less around this time but I
tío será más o menos por esta época pero
don't
no me
remember I don't remember what the
acuerdo no me acuerdo cómo se llamaba el
video was called but it was one of Maichi's too yes yes yes
vídeo pero era un los de maichi también
yes it's that I would love to see
sí sí sí sí es que me encantaría ver
because I think in the same video we
porque creo que en el mismo vídeo
were talking about other things
hablábamos de de más cosas
inside you upload a lot of tasty content
dentro subes mucho contenido vio sabroso
no no no This is it this is the video
no no no Ya esta es este es el vídeo
Look surely on some occasion to
Mira seguramente en alguna ocasión a
bore you noos bore with me
aburriros noos aburrir conmigo
eh bore or not bore with me there
eh aburrir o no aburrir conmigo
was a part ah It's true that they
que había una parte ah Es verdad que
also made a bomb warning
hicieron como un aviso de bomba también
during the
en la
evening the security of the venue was in
velada la seguridad del recinto se
charge of evacuating the entire stadium
encargó de desalojar todo el estadio lo
as quickly and urgently as possible because you
más rápidamente y urgente posible por
never know what it might
aquello de que nunca se sabe lo que pu
seem very funny to send the email
parecido muy gracioso enviar el correo
with the threat but it is already psychopathic and
con La amenaza pero ya es de psicópata y
narcissistic to go to his Twitter account to
narcisista ir a su cuenta de Twitter a
confess what he did thinking that he
confesar lo que hizo pensando que aún
will still go unpunished when they discover
así va a quedar impune cuando descubran
Who he is I am sure that  he could be
Quién es estoy seguro de que podría ser
extradited and sentenced to many years in
extraditado y condenado a muchos años de
prison So from here I want to show
cárcel Así que nada desde aquí mostrarle
my full support to all the youtubers who are
todo mi apoyo a todos los youtubers que
being affected by these types
se están viendo afectados por este tipo
of circumstances I wanted to make this
de circunstancias quería hacer esta
public complaint not only to
denuncia pública no solamente para
show support for my colleagues and to
mostrarle el apoyo a mis compañeros y
denounce and give it visibility so that
para denunciar y darle visibilidad a que
you can see okay well it's the same it's the same
veáis vale pues es el mismo es el mismo
if we're going to we're
si iremos a
going to Creole we are you're going to pay for
iremos a creol somos vas a pagar por
telling them we're going to
decirles iremos
your little sister it won't take a
a tu hermanita pequeña no pasara de una
week legion odmp Japanese demon
semana legón odmp demonio japonés
Japanese demon Hello we are the odar legion
demonio japonés Hola som la legión odar
you're going to pay for saying that to
vas a pagar por decirle eso a
your little sister it won't take
la tu hermanita pequeña no pasará de la
a week dimp let's see friend That's my
una semana le dimp a ver amigo Esa es mi
home address if you want go I'll
dirección de mi casa si querés anda te
wait for you and we'll [ __ ] Piña I
espero y nos cagamos a Piña seguramente
'm probably a 15 year old kid who likes to
so un pibe de 15 años que le gusta
act spicy on the internet you You don't
hacerse el picante por internet vos No
know the amount of people who sent me
sabés la cantidad de gente que me mandó
my address my phone number photos
mi dirección mi número de teléfono fotos
of my dad my mom threatening me every
de mi papá mi mamá amenazándome todos
day that they were going to kill us that
los días de que nos iban a matar que
this and that after that nobody shows up
esto y lo otro después no aparece nadie
nobody shows up why because they live
no aparece nadie por qué Porque viven
behind the computer no  more you there are
atrás de la computadora no más ustedes
real problems there are
hay problemas reales hay problemas
real problems and there are really spicy people in
reales y hay gente picante de verdad en
the street not the same Yeah I mean you're an
la calle de no igual Sí o sea vos sos un
internet hottie because if someone
pivito de internet porque si alguien
really wants to kill me They won't
realmente me quiere matar No me va a
send me a bit donation If someone
mandar donación de bits Si alguien me
wants to kill me they're going to come here and they're going to
quiere matar va a venir acá y me va a
kill me period if you suck my dick and
matar y punto si vos me chupas la pija y
suck my dick your message and suck my
me chupa la pija tu mensaje y me chupa
dick come to my house if you want if you
la pija anda a mi casa si querés si te
give it your all my house I'm going to be
das los huevo mi casa te voy a estar
waiting for you my dad with a great message
esperando mi papá con un gran mensaje
too Come on Come on I'm waiting for you I mean I'm really
también Dale anda Anda Te espero o sea
waiting for you Come on Come on I
realmente te espero Vení Vení realmente
mean I don't have any problem Come on I
Vení O sea no tengo ningún problema Vení
mean you're acting cool dude legion odar
o sea te hac el piola boludo legión odar
What is the legion odar legion of what of
Qué es la legión odar legión de qué de
my balls what are you an empire of the
mis pelotas qué sos un imperio del
jabo.es idiot suck my balls a
jabo.es boludo chupame las bolas un
group of three or four cros Holy God
grupo de tres o cuatro cros Dios santo
idiot these people you know the amount
boludo esta gente vos sabes la cantidad
of times they threatened me with my
de veces que me amenazaron con mi
address my phone number this that thing
dirección mi número de teléfono esto lo
go [ __ ] yourself suck dick eh
otro andate a [__] chupa la pija eh
these people act stupid I love it I
esta gente se hace boludo me encanta me
love it when  they make me
encanta cuando se me hacen los los
angry with that [ __ ] like I'm
picantes con esas boludeces como
thinking that it's the first time they're
pensando que es la primera vez que me lo
doing it to me, I mean really, there are people who
hacen o sea real tipo hay gente que
think that it's the first time they've given me
piensa que es la primera vez que me
my address you know what I mean, friend, I've been
pasan mi dirección me entendés amigo
on the internet making content for 10 years, do
llevo 10 años en internet haciendo
you think this is the first
contenido vos te crees que es la primera
time that they threaten to come to my house
vez que me amenazan con venir a mi casa
to do something to me, do something to me, even my
a hacerme algo hacerme algo hasta mi
sister who's 25, what are you saying? Oh,
hermana que tiene 25 que ahí me decís Ah
your little sister won't be a
tu hermanita pequeña no pasará una
week away. First, I don't have one, her
semana primero no tengo una una her
little sister is bigger than me and second, you
pequeña es más grande que yo y segundo
're going to fight with my sister and my
le vas a pelear a mi hermana y mi
sister will piss you off, you know, you're a
hermana te caga pillas porque vos sos un
scared 15 year old kid behind a
[__] de 15 años asustado atrás de una
screen. Third, thanks for the bits
pantalla tercero gracias por los bits
because you gave me a gift. I'm going to use it to
porque me diste un dó lo voy a usar para
buy toilet paper and uh, wipe my
comprar papel higiénico y eh limpiarme
ass,
el [__]
thanks. It makes me angry even
gracias Es que me da esta coraje incluso
that they give it any kind of attention
que se le dé ningún tipo de atención
because in the end that's what they're looking for, if
porque al final es lo que buscan ya si
Sprint has given them that little bit of
Sprint le ha dado ese
time, if Sprint has given them that little bit of time,
ratito si Sprint le ha dado ese ratito
with that little bit of time they're going to, you know, they're going to
ya con ese ratito ya van a sabes van van
do it again or some kind of move, okay?
a volver a hacerlo o alguna movida vale
Ah  [ __ ] We need to talk about this
Ah [__] Tenemos que hablar de este
topic We also need to talk about this
tema También tenemos que hablar de este
topic too man I posted it I posted a
tema también tío lo puse puse un
tweet I posted it eh I
tweet lo puse eh
posted the news but in the end
ta puse la noticia pero al final no la
we haven't commented on it man yesterday I went out to dinner
hemos comentado tío ayer salía a cenar
with the family and such here's the news
con la family y tal aquí está la noticia
not here okay breaking news a few years ago
no aquí vale última hora hace unos años
the youtuber freedom of whatever arises was
el youtuber libertad de lo que surja fue
accused in a Twitter scratch of
acusado en un scratche de Twitter de
bothering some girls at a nightclub
molestar en una discoteca a unas chicas
and ending up splitting one of
y acabar partiéndole la ceja a una de
their eyebrows with a punch Well there was a
ellas de un puñetazo Pues bien hubo un
trial and the sentence has already come out
juicio y ya ha salido la sentencia
acquitted man I don't even know how many of the
absuelto tío no sé ni a cuántos de los
bad guys who are chasing us I've seen eh
malitos que nos persiguen he visto eh
trust me I don't have a friendship with Adriá I don't
fíate tú que yo no tengo con adriá yo no
have a friendship I mean I know him as a
tengo amistad o sea lo conozco de
colleague here on the platform you know I don't have a friendship I don't
colega de aquí de la plataforma sabes no
talk to him much the truth
tengo no hablo mucho con él la verdad
and but like there are people who
e pero como que hay gente que por
consider what is close to my
considerar lo que está cerca de mi
environment What I don't have a friendship with
entorno Alo que yo no tengo amistad con
him I mean with Adriá is that I don't talk almost at
él o sea con adriá es que no hablo casi
all I mean you know what I'm saying and now
nada o sea sabes lo que te digo y ahora
suddenly I think none of them have said
de repente creo que no han dicho ninguno
anything or at least they haven't said anything to me
nada o por lo menos a mí no me ha
nothing's come of it, it's worth it that
llegado nada vale de que se han pegado
these two or three years have been the
estos dos o tres años que ha sido el
procedure eh that I already knew for a long
procedimiento eh que yo ya sabía de hace
time that the witness was accused of
tiempo que la testigo estaba imputada
false testimony eh
por falso por falso testimonio eh
because it came to me okay but now they haven't
porque me llegó vale pero ahora no han
said a word at all, all those who started
dicho ni mu todos los que se han puesto
to be a [ __ ] pain as if he were already
a dar el [__] [__] como si ya
convicted
estuviera condenado
Okay, well it turns out that there was a trial
Vale pues bueno resulta que hubo juicio
and the sentence has already come out, he was acquitted,
y ya ha salido la sentencia absuelto se
the cameras from the premises were obtained and the
obtuvieron las cámaras del local y la
version that the witnesses gave was
versión que dieron los Testigos era
false, even one of them ended up
falsa incluso uno de ellas ha acabado
sentenced to prison for false
condenada a prisión por falso
testimony according to the facts proven in
testimonio según los hechos probado de
the sentence, the one who suffered injuries was
la sentencia el que sufrió lesiones fue
Adrian okay look how things change
Adrián vale fijaros Cómo cambia la cosa
eh I mean this screenshot from
eh o sea esta captura de pantalla de
this newspaper I don't even know how many times I
este periódico no sé ni Cuántas veces lo
saw it I don't know who would do it who would take
vi no sé quién lo haría quién llevaría
a youtuber breaks a young woman's eyebrow
un youtuber le rompe la ceja a una joven
and here in the newspaper they tell you the
y aquí ya en el periódico te hacen la
story not as the one who
historia no como lo contó la la que lo
told it At that moment no no that Adriá
contó En aquel momento no no que adriá
went to harass her you know eh And he was
fue a acosar le sabes eh Y la estaba
bothering her and how the girl told him to
molestando y como la chica le dijo que
leave him now because he was Even
le dejara ya porque le estaba Incluso
like he was touching her more than necessary  luo that's what it
como que tocaba más de la cuenta luo así
said Well, there was already a fight
ponía No pues que ya hubo una pelea vino
a boyfriend came to tell him something and Adrial
un novio a decirle algo y ya adrial les
hit them I don't know what you know Well, lie okay
pegó no sé qué sabes Bueno pues mentira
lie
vale mentira
Look okay And over here Inc Kai has put
Mira okay Y por aquí Inc Kai ha puesto
something
algo
no people it has been the trial of the
no gente ha sido el juicio de la
aggression at the nightclub and I have
agresión de la discoteca y tengo una
bad news I have bad news for
mala noticia tengo una mala noticia para
all the idiots who believed the
todos los imbéciles que se creyeron la
version of the sub normative progressives I
versión de los progres sub normativos Yo
am innocent just as I told you at the
soy inocente tal y como os conté en su
time you had two versions a
momento tuvisteis dos versiones una
crazy one that these idiots gave and that
loquísima que dieron estos zumbados y
went around in many ways and
que se movió por muchísimos lados y la
mine and it only resulted in a certain ruling that
mía y solo resultó una cierta fallo que
must acquit and I acquit Adrián Núñez
debe absolver y absuelvo a Adrián Núñez
pradas of the less serious crime of
pradas del delito menos grave de
injuries object of
lesiones objeto de
accusation
acusación hecho
proven fact has been proven that t ta so and
probado ha resultado probado que t ta
so on November 28, 2021 at approximately
tal en fecha 28 de noviembre 2021 sobre
6 in the morning was
las 6 de la mañana se hallaba en el
inside the Boveda nightclub
interior de la discoteca bóveda
in the company of tatat so and so and his partner
e en compañía de tatat tal y su pareja
of the latter when Mr. Adi approached them
de esta última cuando se les aproximó el
witnessing How
señor Adi presenciando Cómo se produjo
an argument broke out between estea and her friend the
una discusión entre estea y su amiga el
Lord because Mr.  Núñez was
Señor porque el señor Núñez se
constantly approaching them, an
aproximaba constantemente a ellos
argument that occurred at 6:06 during
discusión producida a las 6:06 en el
which Mr. Núñez
curso del cual el señor Núñez le dio
tapped the lady on the head,
unos golpecitos en la cabeza de la
her partner reacted by
señora reaccionando su pareja que le
opening his hand and the lady hitting him in
apert la mano y la señora que le golpeó
the face and kicking him, to
la cara y le propinó una patada ante lo
which Mr. Núñez punched her
cual el señor Núñez le dio un puñetazo
in the face and her partner hit him
en la cara y la pareja de esta le golpeó
in turn, making him fall to the ground,
a su vez haciéndole caer al suelo
basically they were fighting, okay.
básicamente que se estaban peleando vale
Later here, if you want, we can enter
Ya luego aquí si queréis podemos entrar
into the debate about whether a man should let
en el debate de no es que un hombre si
a woman hit him,
le pega una mujer se le tiene que dejar
okay, if I remember correctly, what
vale si no mal recuerdo lo que dijo
Adria said was like the girl started
adria era como que la chica empezó a
hitting her and her boyfriend was on top of her
golpearla y se vio encima el novio
too, so he did like the
también entonces é hizo como la de El
instinct, not something that was more like a
instinto no algo que fue como más un
reflex action than an
acto reflejo que una que una
intentionality, okay, look at thread from
intencionalidad vale mira hilo del
2021 H, about the assault that I suffered,
2021 H lo de la agresión que he sufrido
okay, yesterday some guys came to me, they
vale ayer unos tipos vinieron a mí me
hit me and I defended myself, today they are acting like a
golpearon y me defendí hoy están en plan
victim, making up a story that
vítima inventándose una historia que
is recorded because it happened in a
está grabada porque ocurrió en una
nightclub, I'll tell you because there is a lot
discoteca os cuento porque hay mucho
Look for tape that goes defaming yesterday I went out
Busca fita que va difamando a ayer salí
to party and I was chatting with a lot of
de fiesta y estuve Charlando con mucha
people Well in one of these that I
gente Pues bien en una de estas que me
start dancing with a girl without more we
pongo a bailar con una chavala sin más
were talking for a while and a
estábamos un rato hablando y me vino un
guy who was a head taller than me came up to me and told me
tipo que me sacaba una cabeza a decirme
not to talk to her obviously sudde
que no hablara con ella obviamente sudde
the first thing you think when you
lo primero que piensas cuando te
find something like this is that the guy
encuentras algo así es que el tipo
wants to flirt see her and you bother him I ignore him and I
quiere ligar seela y le molestas sudo de
continue with my things without more without
él y yo sigo a mis cosas sin más sin
flirting or anything I was chatting the same
ligar ni nada Yo estaba Charlando igual
with her as with other guys plus it
con ella que con otros tíos además que
's obviously absurd that third parties
obviamente es absurdo que terceros
come to tell you anything blah blah blah blah
vengan a decirte nada bla bla bla bla
blah okay Wait I don't want
bla vale Espera que no quiero que se vea
the video down there to be seen
el vídeo que está allí abajo
The prisoner and the people in the group
El reo y el de gente del grupo se me
get threatening me a good mob
pone en plan amenazante una buena turba
of guys and guys and a girl punches me
de tíos y tíos y una chavala me suelta
in the face she did it As
un puñetazo en la cara lo hizo ella Como
any other guy could have done and
podía haberlo hecho cualquier otro tío y
obviously as a reflex I defended myself
obviamente como acto reflejo me defendí
okay I mean
vale o sea
[Music]
[Música]
um well uh Eh Well nothing has won I do
em bueno eh Eh Pues nada que ha ganado
n't know I don't know if I have  any more topics in
no sé no sé si tengo algún tema más en
today's title because I feel a
el título de hoy porque me encuentro un
little Oh I have the Barral thing man I have to
poco Ay tengo lo de barral tío tengo que
see the Barral thing it's that I feel a
ver lo de barral es que me encuentro un
little bad but man let's listen to
poco mal pero hombre vamos a escuchar lo
Barral's thing that I would like I would like to
de barral que me gustaría me gustaría
hear what it is What is the excuse
escuchar que es lo que Cuál es la excusa
you give did you see the tweet that Adriá sent you
pones viste el twit que te puso adriá
when you said that he won No Tobia what did he put what did he put
cuando dijiste que él ganó No tobía qué
let's put it live right now to this
vamos a ponerlo ahorita en vivo a este
te clab let's write to him here I
te clab vamos a escribirle aquí
am here
estoy aquí
okay
vale sala de
beating room How annoying Tell him I'm here
batir Qué pesado Dígale que estoy aquí
Tell him I'm here and to come Tell him I
Dígale que estoy aquí y que venga Dígale
'm here and to come debate
que estoy aquí y que venga a debatir
Tell him I'm here and to come
Dígale que estoy aquí y que venga a
debate this miserable rat has
debatir esta rata miserable otra vez se
come by my channel again has come by
ha pasado por mi canal se ha pasado por
my channel and I don't know what saying that I've
mi canal y no sé qué diciendo que yo le
been scared of him and I've been scared
he tenido miedo y yo le he tenido miedo
saying that I've been scared of him
diciendo que yo le he tenido miedo dí
go go to the Channel of this miserable rat
váyanse al Canal de esta rata miserable
called Javi Oliviera that I'm
que se llama Javi oliviera que estoy en
live and I'm waiting for him go
vivo y lo estoy esperando vayan a
tell him go tell him that I'm
decirle vayan a decirle que estoy en
live and I am  waiting especially for the
vivo y lo estoy esperando sobre todo la
people of Twitch go tell him that
gente de Twitch vayan a decirle que
I'm live and I'm waiting for him for that
estoy en vivo y lo estoy esperando a esa
miserable rat go tell him that I'm
rata miserable vayan a decirle que estoy
live and I'm waiting for him go
en vivo y lo estoy esperando vayan a
tell him that I'm live and I'm
decirle que estoy en vivo y lo estoy
waiting for him while that miserable rat
esperando mientras esa rata miserable
comes out we already know we already know that these
Sale ya sabemos ya sabemos que estas
miserable rats don't come that they're
ratas miserables no vienen que tienen
afraid that they're afraid they're afraid of
miedo que tiene miedo tien miedo al
ridicule that's why they don't come in they're afraid go say go tell him go tell him
ridículo por eso no V entr tienen miedo
go tell him that I'm
decirle vayan a decirle que lo estoy
waiting for him go tell him tell him that I
esperando vayan a decirle decirle que le
'm waiting for him Ah to chat I need
estoy esperando Ah para chatear necesito
this what's this called to be the
este cómo se llama este ser el
subscriber I don't know what to see olive and the other one
suscriptor no sé qué ver oliva y la otra
who was defending him is called cat what the [ __ ] go go
que lo defendía se llama gato qué [__]
I'm live miserable rats V
go estoy en vivo ratas miserables V
comment it tag both of them tag
coméntenlo etiquet a los dos etiqu a los
both go there are idiots who are into something
dos va hay estúpidos que que le va
well And this miserable rat hasn't
cosita bueno Y esta rata miserable ya no
said anything I already read it Tell him that I
ha dicho nada Ya me le yo Díganle que lo
'm watching him and I'm waiting for him Ah I already
estoy viendo y lo estoy esperando Ah ya
read that he stopped by my Twitter
me le yo que se ha pasado por mi Twitter
and I don't know what What does this miserable rat make a living
y no sé qué Ya de qué Vive esta rata
from talking about others that's what he makes his
miserable de hablar de los demás de eso
living from Ah that's what  He lives off of talking about
vive Ah de eso vive de hablar de los
others, that's what he lives off of, that's what he lives off of, that's what he lives off of talking
demás de eso vive de eso vive de hablar
about others, gossip if
de los demás del chisme si le alcanza
he can afford to buy 000 if what he earns on Twitch is enough to buy $1,000
Twitch si le alcanza para comprar $1,000
of pic Coin Ah I saw the gossip Ah yeah
de pic Coin Ah vi de los chismes Ah ya
Why do I have to buy 100,000 of
Por qué tengo que comprar 100,000 de
panic Coin is panic Coin to buy
panic Coin está panic Coin para comprar
000 today let's go connect to tiktok
000 hoy vamos que se conecte a tiktok
put his phone number and connect
que ponga su teléfono y que se conecte
to tiktok to put it on four
de tiktok para ponerlo en cuatro
quickly this miserable rat talked and
rapidito esta rata miserable hablaba y
talked not that he was promoting p this miserable rat
hablaba no que promocionaba p esta rata
that this Javier olivea this miserable rat
miserable que este Javier olivea esta
who is here right now
rata miserable que está ahorita aquí en
live right here live was promoting
vivo ahorita aquí en vivo promocionaba
picin this
picin esta rata
miserable rat go tell him that I'm waiting for him
miserable vayan a decirle que lo estoy
go tell him that I'm
esperando vayan a decirle que lo estoy
waiting for him this rat
esperando esta rata
my saying that I'm waiting for him go
mis decir que lo estoy esperando vay
tell him that I'm waiting for him that that that keep running keep running
decirle que lo estoy esperando eso eso
r keep running keep running keep running
que sigan corriendo sigan corriendo r
rats keep running keep
corriendo ratas sigan corriendo sig
running keep talking about something else keep
corriendo sigando sigue hablando de otra
talking about something else Let's see
cosa sigue hablando de otra cosa A ver
let's see what
vamos a ver lo que ha dicho
barral said about what we saw
barral sobre lo que vimos
yesterday  This is not that we are not going, it is not the
ayer Esto no es que no vamos no es no es
same as the other, there is the organization and I
igual que lo otro está la organización y
ask, I say this is not that we are not going No, it is not the
pido digo esto no es que no vamos No no
same as the other That sanction is not the
es igual que lo otro Esa sanción no es
same as Juan's Ah, he wanted
la misma que la de Juan Ah que él quería
Juan to receive the same sanction as
que a Juan le pusieran la misma sanción
him, man I think not, I think
que a él hombre Yo creo que no yo creo
Juan did not do the same as him What
que Juan no hizo lo mismo que él Qué
happened here is not that Juan is the president
pasó aquí no es que Juan es presidente
Juan is the cold team of Mexico and we
Juan es el equipo enfrión de México y no
cannot sanction him okay
lo podemos sancionar bueno
okay It's not that, it's that apart from the fact that he is
vale No es que es que aparte de que es
president, he is not
presidente no es
eh It's not the
eh No es lo
same I consider that it is not the same
mismo Considero que no es lo mismo
okay it also bothers me it bothered me a
vale también me molesta me ha molestado
little Well a little no a little quite a bit
poco Bueno un poco no un poco bastante
that Piqué Piqué was the one who
que Piqué Piqué haya sido el que ha
uploaded the video to his social networks
subido a sus redes sociales el vídeo
because there he leaves one person in evidence
porque ahí deja en evidencia a una
but he does not include the insults of the
persona pero no pone los insultos de la
other, you know, you do not include the insults of the
otra sabes no pones los insultos de el
president of annihilators you
presidente de aniquiladores pones
only include the insult of eche Put both
solamente el insulto de eche Pon los dos
judge them both equally and since the
juzga a los dos por igual y ya que la
people decide or that or that or that upload it
gente decida o que o que o que lo suba
Kill but you do not have to upload it
la Kill pero no tienes por qué subirlo
in your in your  personal platform is
tú en tu en tu plataforma personal es
that it is out of place but well
que está fuera fuera fuera de lugar pero
as the kinly is a show and it is a
bueno como la kinly es un show y es una
way to entertain people, the
forma de de entretener a la gente pues
more controversy and the more
contra más polémica y contra más
external factors there are, the
factores externos haya pues seguramente
more views they will surely have and the more
más visualizaciones vayan a tener y más
money they will
dinero
earn. It also
ganen también me
bothers me Piqu they have charged him in a
molesta piqu lo han imputado en una
move what was it I saw it on
movida qué es lo que fue lo vi en el
Pulsito's Twitter it
Twitter de pulsito
happens that nobody is commenting on it I don't know
pasa que nadie lo está comentando no sé
why
por qué
But this Chito no this no Look Piqué
Pero esto Chito no esto no Mira Piqué
charged for the Saudi Arabian commissions
imputado por las comisiones de Arabia
the judge appreciates that there are indications
saudí la jueza aprecia que hay indicios
of a crime when receiving the 4
de delito al recibir la comisión de 4
million euro commission for transferring the
millones de euros por trasladar la
Spanish Super Cup Saudi Arabia el
supercopa de España Arabia saudí el
confidencial but apart from this
confidencial pero es que aparte de esto
Piquet did not have a move, in other words this is the
piquet no tenía una movida o sea esto es
same as Rubiales it
lo mismo que lo de rubiales
is the
es lo
same as closing him down he keeps talking about something
mismo que cierres el sigue hablando de
else I am going to keep crushing you
otra cosa te voy a seguir machacando
keep talking about something else keep talking about something else
sigue hablando de otra cosa sigue
miserable rat
hablando de otra cosa rata miserable
talking about something else miserable rat you
hablando de otra cosa rata miserable ya
can no longer justify the unjustifiable
no se puede justificar lo injustificable
gentlemen, that simple d review he came off
señores así de simple d review quedó
as a cheap thief now
como un un ladrón barato ya ladrón
cheap thief because if you follow me
barato porque ya si ustedes me siguen
you have money that time [ __ ]
ustedes tienen plata ese tiempo follando
or whatever look like before
o lo que fuera mir como antes
walking this [ __ ] you
deando esta hev
don't know how to say that the more I was alone the
no sabes cómo decir que más estuve a mi
more I was disconnected the
bola que más estuve desconectada que
less this [ __ ] wants to debate
menos estaba esta huevada quiere debatir
with me you lubricious felon you have an
conmigo lúbrico felón tienes un
extra chromosome or a repeated chromosome
cromosoma de más o un cromosoma repetido
this [ __ ] wants to beat me This
esta huevada quiere batir conmigo Este
is the content of this [ __ ] gossip I'm
es el contenido de esta [__] chismes
going to [ __ ] gossip This is the content
voy a cul chismes Este es el contenido
of this [ __ ] gossip it even makes me feel ashamed
de esta [__] chismes hasta me da pena
What a shame this son of a [ __ ] owes you
Qué pena este hijo de [__] pena te debe
to all the people he scammed well
de a toda la gente que estafó pues
talking about bitcoin bread that's what you should feel
hablando de pan bitcoin de eso te debe
ashamed of all the people he scammed
dar pena de toda la gente que te estafó
eh eh When when he was promoting
eh eh Cuando cuando promocionaba pan
bitcoin bread Well that's what you should feel
bitcoin Pues de eso te tiene que dar
ashamed of now that's what you should feel ashamed of
pena ya de eso te tiene que dar pena de
all the people he scammed says
todas las la gente que estafó dice el
Javi Ah he's leaving No he's leaving let him keep
Javi Ah ya se va No ya se va que siga
running miserable rat that day that day
corriendo rata miserable ese día ese día
I was talking about wings Yes I saw
yo estaba hablando este de alas Sí vi
that someone told me me me Javi
que alguien me me me me comentó Javi
Javi is watching you you l didn't know who
Javi te está viendo tu l no sabía quién
candy Javi well it's nice  that
chuchera Javi pues est simpática esa
bald thing But hey let's continue guys let's
pelada Pero bueno sigamos muchachos
continue yesterday You had the opportunity of 5
sigamos ayer Tuviste la oportunidad de 5
minutes of fame with 3500 spectators
minutos de fama con 3500 espectadores
3500 idiots who lost money on
3500 imbéciles que perdieron plata en
bread bicin how many people see me well I'm going to
pan bicin cuánta gente me ve bien voy a
do well you lost money
hacer bien perdieron plata
peak per 100 people see me you
pico per me ven 100 personas ustedes
Sons Javi you look for every host but it's that you
Sons Javi te buscas cada [__] pero es
are peculiar it's that let's see it's that we
que son peculiares es que a ver es que
always have this magnet but of course it's that
siempre tenemos este imán pero claro es
I understand that this is what the
que yo entiendo que esto es que es
internet is no I don't know and on the internet how do we have
internet no no sé y en internet como
the window here open to all
tenemos la ventana aquí abierta a a todo
this no you only there are 175 right now 100
esto no tú no más hay 175 ahorita 100
lions are better than 3500
leones son mejor que 3500 borregos
[ __ ] sheep who put their money in bread
retrasados que meten su plata en pan
bitcoin yes let him keep running all his
bitcoin sí que siga corriendo toda su
life keep running all his life
vida siga corriendo toda su vida rata
miserable rat his channels of pure [ __ ] like
miserable su canales de pura [__] así
pure gossip, I mean this [ __ ] rat already
de puro chisme o sea esta [__] rata ya
with two neurons with two neurons one
con dos neuronas con dos neuronas la una
neuron to speak and the other to [ __ ]
neurona para hablar y la otra para [__]
but he shits through his mouth now he wants to debate
pero caga por la boca ya quiere debatir
with me Let him [ __ ] around Let him [ __ ] around Let him
conmigo Déjate huevar Déjate huevar Ya
[ __ ] around he's live  the
déjate huevar está en directo el
turkey is live the turkey
pavo está en directo el pavo
still Javi is not worth a lawsuit because
todavía Javi no da para una demanda pues
that guy is not from Spain
ese tío no es de España
no if he were Spanish I understand that yes
no si fuera español entiendo que sí
man with that
hombre con esa
mouth if he were Spanish yes
boca si fuera español sí
But wow last night I wrote a lawsuit I
Pero buah anoche redacté una demanda
wrote a lawsuit Yeah well to
redacté una demanda Sí bueno para
send it to the
mandárselo al
lawyer and I was there until 8 in the
abogado y estuve hasta las 8 de la
morning man But well that topic is over
mañana tío Pero bueno se acabó ese tema
although they are right about Dallas
aunque tengan razón en lo de Dallas por
why do they insult Dallas why do they insult
qué insultan a Dallas por qué insultan a
Javi I don't understand that I have not
Javi No entiendo que yo no he
promoted anything on the contrary I think I have
promocionado nada al contrario creo que
repeated like 500 times that I do not
he repetido como 500 veces que yo no
recommend to anyone that I am not into
recomiendo a nadie que no estoy metido
the world of Christ that you put anything in
en el mundillo de Cristo que metáis nada
Ah if you have money to spare and you want to try
Ah si te sobra la pasta y quieres probar
like in a casino you understand
como en plan casino me entiendes pero en
but in a casino way literally you know if you want to put in I don't know 100 bucks 200 bucks to say jump and you don't care about losing it you understand But he never No I have not But how am I going to promote something that is having a reach right now in which all the channels
alcance en la que todos los canales
I have to make the rent yes that's true I have to
tengo que hacer la renta sí es verdad
do that all the
Esa tengo que hacerla que todos los
channels are talking to each other  of topic What what
canales de se están hablando de tema
's my promo mention it talk
Cuál cuál es mi promo mencionarlo hablar
about the topic I think he's Venezuelan he's already won his
del tema creo que es venezolano ya ganó
minutes of fame Yeah yeah Well but
los minutos de fama Sí sí Bueno pero es
the guy is so hungry
que el tío tiene un hambre que no veas
man I mean the guy is giving you 8000 tweets
tío o sea el tío está te pone 8000 tweet
every minute loving me I don't
cada minuto m queriéndome yo que
know wanting collaboration the poor thing
sé queriendo colaboración el pobre
eh Cry went to Cry went to Kick
eh Cry se fue a Cry se fue a Kick
I'm also getting out here
también me está saliendo por aquí
Okay guys I'm going I feel a little
Bueno chicos me voy me encuentro un poco
bad man I don't know if it's because I haven't
regulín tío No sé si es porque no he
rested well or what but I feel
descansado bien o qué pero me encuentro
a little bad plus it hurts
un poco de regulín además que me duele
man it hurts my stomach hurts man
tío me duele me duele la barriga tío
but it's really
pero muy
weird because it's like they're like abdominal pains man
raro porque es como son como dolores tío
but when I breathe the
abdominales pero cuando respiro el
air you know I don't know I feel a little
aire sabes no sé me encuentro un poco
bad I'm going to I'm going to go to bed you haven't
mal me voy a me voy a ir a la cama no
slept much it's just that last night I had to
has dormido mucho es que anoche tuve que
do a lot of things I'll tell you about it but it's
hacer muchas cosas ya lo contaré pero es
a thing that has to stop all and that
una movida que hay que parar all y que
has to stop once and for all I should have
hay que frenar de una vez Tena que
done it a long time ago and I will do it
haberlo hecho hace tiempo y ya lo haré
you went overboard with the abs Okay yes
te pasaste con los abdominales Bueno sí
you think they could be bujetas
ustedes creen que pueden ser abujetas
could they be  We are giving it a go, of
pueden ser que sea le estamos dando caña
course, with our bellies in front. No,
claro con con la barriga por delante no
guys, see you tomorrow. A kiss, handsome.
chicos nos vemos mañana un beso guapos
Thanks for the company. Bye. Well,
Gracias por la compañía chao Bueno
tomorrow, I hope not.
mañana ojalá que no an